SAMUEL GOLDWYN FILMS
NIKKATSU
INFINITE STUDIOS
ZHAO WEI FILMS
BERT PICTURES
For centuries, the
ancient lands of Indonesia
were colonized by
the Dutch Empire.
Accounts of suppression,
brutality and tragedy
are often lost in
taes of folkore.
This is one story where the
worlds of fact and fiction collide...
CALIFORNIA, TAHUN 1860
Ayo, ya pasang
semuanya! Ya begitu!
3 banding 1
untuk pria kecil ini.
Percayalah, yang bisa
melipat-tigakan uangmu, mau?
Melipat-tigakan
uangmu, cukup gila 'kan.
Ini pertarungan tingkat
banding yang ekstrim.
Kalian siap untuk
pertarungan ini?
Ada lagi? / Dia akan
pertaruhkan semua uangnya.
Ayo.
Coba tendang
lebih keras lagi, kak.
Ya begitu.
Ooh!
Sebaiknya menyerah sekarang
selagi gigimu masih utuh, kak.
Terus saja kumpulkan
taruhannya, aku belum selesai.
Kau yakin? / Oh!
Taruhan diganti, 7 banding 1.
Terasa baikan?
Ya begitu!
Sekarang aku baru
selesai. / Pertarungan bagus.
Baiklah.
Jangan lupa bagianku.
/ Kita sudah bunuh satu.
Sialan, kau curang.
Pertarungan dicurangi.
Kau sama tahunya dengan aku kalau
pertarungan kami menangkan dengan adil.
Omong kosong.
Kembalikan uang kami.
Santai, ini cuma permainan, nak.
Kami kembalikan uangmu.
Tapi biarkan kami melanjutkan
perjalanan kami dengan damai.
Oh tidak, bos. Ini
keretaku. / Keretamu?
Aku yang kerjakan jalur
kereta ini bersama anak-anakku
sejak kau masih menetek ibumu.
Brengsek kau...
Paman!
Paman! Sial, Suwo!
Biar kulihat, biar kulihat!
Maaf.
Cuma tergores, kau tak apa-apa.
Ya. / Tak apa.
Maafkan aku.
Sekarang saatnya kita pulang.
Aku tak mau mati... sebelum
kita selesaikan masalah ini.
BUFFALO BOYS
JAVA, 6 MONTHS LATER
Hey, Suwo.
I though I'd never return to
kiss the earth of my homeland
that I had left behind.
Anak-anak, ingatlah
tujuan kita disini.
Tak ada yang kenal siapa
kita, dan dari mana kita berasal.
Jangan percaya
siapapun, membaurlah.
Dan ingat, gunakan bahasa
ibumu seperti yang kuajarkan.
Come, let's go.
Hurry!
Kapal tak bisa
menunggu seharian.
Ayo.
Ayo, kalian.
First, we must pay our
respect to your faher
at the final resting place of
all Sultans and their families.
This is your father's grave
and this... your mother's.
God bless her soul.
Seruni.
Forgive me.
I should have never left you.
A long time ago,
ancient kings ruled this land.
Civilization here flourished
a thousand years before us.
We come from a land
deep with heritage.
And part of it runs
through your blood.
Both of you are born
of noble heritage.
Raised in foreign lands,
united by extreme circumtances.
That day, your father
and I managed to escape.
We were lucky,
so you survived.
I thought if we could
negotiate with them
they would leave us in peace.
How naive.
They need to pay.
No.
We've already lost
many of our people today.
Let's not lose our future too.
They're here.
Just get in! Get in!
Get in, Hamza.
Go now.
I'll delay them.
No, Hamza, we move together.
Arana.
Get as far away as you can.
Bring my boys up as your own.
Save them, Arana.
They are our only hope.
Kulihat kau
bertahan dari belatiku,
Sultan Hamza.
My death shall only
strengthen the will of my people.
Van Trach.
Jamar.
As the eldest son, you have
to shoulder the responsibility.
Suwo.
As the youngest
it is your brotherhood bon
that will strengthen
the both of you.
Don't ever forget that.
Apa yang kau lakukan?
/ Huh? Oh, aku...
Jangan main-main.
/ Bukan, tadi aku...
Jangan bikin jengkel.
Anak-anak... sudahlah.
Kau masih terobsesi
dengan peta itu?
Bagaimana kalau
dia tak ada di sana.
Kita akan cari dia...
dimanapun dia berada.
Dan kali ini, kita pasti siap.
Shh.
What do you want?
Do you guys need...
You came from over there.
Heading towards there.
So why are you stopping here?
Everything OK? /
What are you looking at?
Everything is fine.
That's my wife. She's in labor.
She's in labor? / Ya.
I can help. / How?
What's that? / I have medicine.
What medicine?
This is for the pain. / My wife
is not in pain, shes just in labor.
But... / Move along!
Sorry, sir.
We'll move along.
Help!
Don't move!
Or Fakar will kill her! /
Calm down. Calm down.
You want to die?
Get back!
You think Fakar's
messing around?
Think again.
Get back!
Come here.
Sri!
It hurts! / Next time,
mind your own business.
Wait, wait.
Where are you heading?
Please come to our village.
There, you can
bathe, eat, and rest.
That would be my honor.
Please, come.
Hiya!
Ho!
What's happening there?
Anak-anak...
That man knows how to ride.
I've never seen a man
ride buffalo like that.
And shoot like an
Apache warrior! / Yeah.
Woo!
Hiya!
Earlier, I noticed crops being.
Why?
To grow opium.
It's more profitable for them.
If we don't burn the rice
the Dutch will burn us.
Whoa.
There are the farmers
who chose to plant crop
because they though
feeding their families
was more important.
But they had to pay the price.
What's that smell?
This is the stenc...
of hatred.
Hey!
Hiya!
Oh!
Come here, sweetheart.
Grandpa.
What happened to your head?
I had a fall. It's
just a scratch.
Gentlemen,
my grand daughter, Kiona.
You are an excellent rider.
For a...
girl.
Bawakan topiku.
Your riding was spectacular.
I'm Suwo.
Suwo, the hand that you kisses
is the hand that
wipes her... / Ass.
Your beauty made them
forget their manners.
I am Arana.
How's my riding, Grandpa?
Kiona.
You stole my buffalo again?
I only borrowed him, Father.
Your father is the head of the village
while you ride buffaloes as if you're a boy.
You embarrass me.
Excuse me.
You should be proud of her.
Who are you people? / Kiona.
Sri.
Father, don't... / Silence!
What do you want here? / Sakar.
These men are our
friends, not our enemies.
They are... / They
are strangers.
And all strangers are enemies.
If the Dutch finds out we'll
be the ones who pay the price.
Have you no shame.
These men saved me
and your daughter Sri.
That's two lives you owe them.
It's true, Father.
If not for them, both
of us would be dead.
Forgive me.
I misjudged you.
Come join us for dinner tonight.
Would you like to freshen up?
Ah.
Boys, stop showing off.
The ladies are
getting over-excited.
Handsome.
We've met before.
Where? / In my dreams.
I wouldn't forget a
dashing man like that.
Maybe you'll remember
once he takes off his sarong.
Boys...
Let me help you, handsome.
It won't take long. / Boys.
These men saved my family.
Henceforth, we will
treat them as our family.
Yes.
Sir, with all due respect,
your father and daughter
should not be travelling alone.
I would have sent men
to accompany them,
but all our men are
assisting to re-plant the crops.
What?
Assisting?
It's forced labor.
Forced labor? / You've seen what
happens if we dare to oppose them.
Why doesn't the
Sultan do something?
We haven't had a
Sultan for a while.
It suits the Dutch just fine.
The Dutch control
everything now.
Father, Kiona!
You say too much!
Don't you dare
silence me, Sakar.
Our villagers will starve
if we don't have rice.
This is hell on earth.
Ever since Van Trach returned.
Van Trach? / He
and his men kill, rap
and pillage, without
fear of punishment.
Kiona!
And nore of us
dare to fight them.
Kiona!
Don't pay attention to
my daughter's words.
There's a lot she still
doesn't understand.
As long as we
live by their rules
we'll live in peace and
they'll leave us alone.
"As long as we
live by their rules"
"we'll live in peace".
I believed that once.
But the consequence was...
a life was lost.
Damn it!
I don't need help.
I can manage.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be
inside with the other men
making important decisions.
I don't usually
get to participate
in making important decisions.
Oh, yeah.
It's tough, not being
taken seriously.
What would you know about
that? / I mean, I know how you feel.
I can relate.
Can you really? / As the youngest,
I am also at a disadvantage.
No, you have one huge advantage.
You're a man.
You can do whatever you want
whenever you want,
however you want
and with whomever you want.
You're not seen as
an embarrassment
nor evaluated, and not judge.
And all that is because...
you're a man.
You don't think there's
pressure being a man?
I was born with a set of rules.
Don't show your feeling.
Be braver, be stronger.
Fight, be a hero, win.
As if those are the only
virtues that make you a man.
The key is timing.
You're rushin
and therefore, your aim is off.
Are you saying you
have better aim?
Of course.
I'm a man. / Arrogant!
Like this.
I only want to help.
I'm so happy to see you.
You've been gone for so long.
Distance has forced
me to grow up.
Father, Kiona.
I'm tired of hiding.
Moving from village to
village is really tough.
I only want to come home.
We just don't want
you to experience
what we had gone through here.
Though I'm glad you are here.
I also fear for your safety.
They are coming!
Ayo pergi.
You must leave now.
Kiona!
Quick! Guide them to the forest.
There's no time. /
I'm going with Sri.
It's worse if they
find her with them.
But... / Go.
Go!
Suwo! / Ready.
That's enough.
Cover it with leaves.
Yes, Uncle.
Hurry up!
Sir
these are the people,
along with three others
who attacked Fakar.
Sir, this is not true.
Not true? / He attacked us.
Silence!
Where are the others? /
Sir, he tried to rape me.
Who will you believe, sir?
Fakar, your loyal servant
who lost an eye for the company.
Or...
this cursed whore.
Let go!
Don't! Don't!
Sri.
She's not even registered.
No stamp.
It's true, sir.
There were three other people
here but they've gone now.
Fakar was right!
Please, sir
don't harm her.
She has nothing to do with this.
What are you waiting for?
Register her. / Help, sir!
Don't, sir!
Step aside!
What's happening?
Registration.
For what?
Their stamp on us.
We didn't register Sri.
She was too young.
Come!
Sri!
Hurry up!
Where's the little boy, come?
Who's that man?
His name is Drost.
Van Trach's right-hand man.
Don't run!
Take the old man and the girl.
Kiona...
Just leave me.
Come.
Leave her be.
Take the bags.
Forgive me, Sri.
Tomorrow we'll explore the town.
I am sure, Uncle.
Van Trach will be there. / Hmm.
The time for reckoning is here.
Prediksi Togel Jitu, Terbukti JP tiap hari
aplikasi android bit.ly/togelandroid
This is it, boys.
That's all the rice you
get for that little opium.
Go get some supplies.
I will scout around.
Kalian dari mana? Mari masuk.
Banyak barang bagus di dalam.
Mari.
Masuklah.
Welcome, gentlemen.
Sir.
I have something
very special for you.
You are sure to like this.
Try this, Scorpion arak.
Makes you strong.
Makes the ladies feel good.
If there's one
thing I don't like,
it's that.
Scorpions.
Relax, sir. Relax.
Sir.
This just came in.
It is a bit pricey.
But...
You can use this
over and over again.
You pay more
but you can last longer.
Count this.
Sir, come buy some chickens.
How much?
This flower only bloom at night.
Kiona?
What are you doing here?
Besides breeding bulls,
Father also grows flowers.
Any news about your
grandfather and sister?
No news yet
just that all the headmen
have been summoned to town.
Will Van Trach be there?
He should be.
He summoned my
father specifically.
Come with me.
I was about to go
to the town square.
What's going on?
Grandpa.
Sri.
Van Trach.
Tuan-tuan...
kita semua sepakat untuk
mengurusi masyarakat
berdasar keadilan dan
kesejahteraan bersama.
Namun salah satu kalian telah
membiarkan desanya mengecewakan.
Salah satu kalian tak setia.
Sakar... majulah.
Putrimu menghindari registrasi.
Dia dan ayahmu bersekongkol
dengan penjahat asing
dan merampok salah satu
anak buahku disaat patroli rutin.
Penjahat, yang
singgah di desamu.
Warga sekalian...
aku tak bekerja keras
bertahun-tahun ini
untuk melihat kalian semua
terjerumus kembali dalam anarki
di tempat aku
menyelamatkan kalian.
Hukum tetaplah hukum.
Dan harus ditegakkan.
Aku menemukan
pelaku yang bersalah.
Dan hukumannya sudah jelas...
hukuman mati.
No!
Sekarang seperti
kalian semua tahu
aku ini pengampun.
Sebagai Penduduk,
aku bisa mengampuni.
Sayangnya...
aku hanya bisa ampuni
salah satu dari mereka.
Katakan, kawanku...
...siapa yang harus kuampuni.
Sir.
I have serve you well.
Katakan, Sakar.
Jika kau memang setia,
kau tak akan ragu berkata.
Please, Sir.
I did everything you asked.
I cannot make this
impossible choice.
They are my family, sir.
They have done nothing wrong.
Quiet, Sakar!
Why are you
bargaining with the devil?
I am ready to die, Sakar.
But why you have
to beg to this dog!
Why?
Hey, devil invader.
Just kill me!
No, grandpa.
You will rot in
hell soon enough.
Don't.
Apa beban pemimpin
terlalu berat bagimu?
Apa kami harus membebaskanmu
dari tugas untuk sementara?
Yes.
Sakar, kau pasti kenal
baik aku sekarang.
Kau jauh lebih lama mengabdi padaku
dibanding bertindak ini terhadapmu.
Father!
Not here! Too many people.
Cowards!
All of you are cowards!
Kiona, di mata hukum
tindakan ayahmu dianggap
pengkhianatan serius.
aku tak punya pilihan lain
selain menghukum mati dia.
Sebenarnya kuingin
melihat rasa terima kasih
karena mengampuni
nyawa adikmu tercinta.
Apa kau tak mau berterima kasih
Kiona?
Jangan paksa aku
mencabut pengampunanku.
I am thankful.
Aku tak dengar.
I am thankful, sir.
Bawa masuk gadis
baru ini ke dalam rumah.
We have to follow him.
Latih gadis baru itu.
Hai.
It's risky, hiding out here.
It's still the closest
we can get to him.
Have you found us a way out?
Don't worry. The cute
girls downstairs told me this.
There is an exit, at the back.
Mm.
Now we wait.
Sit down, Suwo.
I want to speak
to the two of you.
I have waited for this day.
This dagger belonged
to your father.
This dagger has been
handed down for generations
to each successive Sultan.
And now, you are
its rightful owner.
The Javanese carry
them for protection.
Bring it with you
everywhere you go.
Always keep it with you.
Suwo.
All these years,
I've kept this knife.
It serves as a reminder to me
of the sacrifice and
the pain I've endured.
This is now yours.
We all have the same purpose.
We must work together
to reach our goal.
Remember that well.
I have him.
Relax.
Inhale.
Slow.
Then be sure.
Ready.
Be sure.
There's... There's
a servant in the way.
I can't get a clear shot, Uncle.
I'll do it.
Die, you son of a bitch!
Uncle?
Don't!
Uncle!
Paman! / Paman, hey.
What's wrong?
Suwo, go to the Chinese
store. Get medicine.
Uncle.
OK. OK. / I'll look
for another way.
Prediksi Togel Jitu, Terbukti JP tiap hari
aplikasi android bit.ly/togelandroid
I'm so sorry.
Your father and
grandfather were brave men.
You see that old
lady over there?
Van Trach's gang killed her son.
Or rather, hunted
him down for pleasure.
They returned his
bullet-ridden bod
but without his head.
The bar owner likes
keeping it as a trophy.
She can't rest until
her son is whole again.
But no one can help her.
This is our life living
under Van Trach's rule.
You're the pretty girl
Fakar talked about?
I want to introduce you...
to some of our hungry boys.
Come.
Hey...
Itu pacarmu?
You!
Long time to see.
Duduk.
Diam.
Cyclops. What are you doing?
Looking for lice. Why?
If you plan on blowing his
brains out all over my bar
you better think twice.
Fine.
Fakar is watching you.
I've been watching you.
What do you want here?
Suwo, watch out!
Lihat, kau lihat?
You have balls of steel.
Coming into my bar like that.
Fine.
I'll leave.
But first...
How about that trophy...
and the girl over there...
In exchange for your lives.
You're funny.
But it seems, the
collection on my wall
will be much better...
with another skull.
Suwo.
What's happening here?
You must be ready. He
might come to you tonight.
Why are you still here?
We can find a way to escape.
Many have tried.
They are always captured
and hung on the
Banyan tree outside.
How can you stand this?
My husband
and my entire
family have vanished.
I have no one else but myself.
No one else.
Kau tahu, aku selalu
bersikap lembut padamu.
Kau satu-satunya orang
yang tak berusaha lari.
Mungkin itu sifat cerdas
yang bisa kukagumi.
Indah bukan?
Kuambil kalung ini
karena ini hadiah ibuku dari
seorang pengagum rahasianya.
Dia tak pernah memakainya
karena takut pada ayahku.
Tapi dia menyimpannya,
karena ini yang paling dekat
dan membuat dia bahagia.
Dan oleh karena itu...
kuingin kau memakainya.
I'm not your mother.
I do not want to be
linked to your past.
Dasar sundal!
Where are you going?
To clear my head
get some air.
Wait, Uncle. Look.
Kami menangkap orang asing itu.
Go find Suwo.
Aren't you coming, Uncle?
No.
Meet me at the village later.
Van Trach?
Find your brother first. Go.
Kalian, ikut aku.
Ah.
Katakan yang kau ketahui
tentang pria-pria itu?
Siapa mereka?
You won't get
anything out of me.
Kurasa registrasi
stempelnya perlu diperbarui.
Fakar will get the brand ready.
Don't!
Use the knife.
Oh.
Tunggu! Dari mana
kau mendapatkan itu?
It's not Fakar's.
It was on the table.
It belongs to him.
Dari mana kau menemukan ini?
Answer!
Think hard.
Where did you last leave it.
Sultan Hamza.
Siapa dirimu, bocah?
I am his son.
Anaknya?
Aku sangat ingat hari itu.
Sir...
there's an intruder
in your house.
Arana?
Urus dia, habisi dia.
Thank you, sir.
Kau tetap disini.
You're not in hurry, are you?
Leave him! He's had enough.
Stop torturing him. / I
see, you want one too?
Where do you want
Fakar to put yours?
How about here?
Or should Fakar go
for your forehead?
Yes.
The forehead will do.
Are you all right?
Thank you.
Selalu menyelamatkanmu, huh?
Kenapa kau lama sekali?
Kau tak apa-apa?
Kita harus pergi.
I thought Van Trach
had surely killed you.
He might as well have.
How did you find the strength?
With every beat of my heart
you were there
with me too, Arana.
You were my hope.
There has not been a
single day when I don't regret.
And ask God for forgivenes
for leaving you.
My love.
Seruni...
Van Trach.
Dobrak!
Mereka sudah pergi.
Come! Hurry.
Hide.
Thank you.
Uncle.
Suwo.
Are you all right?
You must be Jamar.
You have your father's eyes.
You're that woman...
at Van Trach house?
It's OK, Jamar.
She's his wife?
I am Seruni.
Your uncle's wife.
But we thought
you were... / Yes.
We all did, but...
Seruni is alive.
You look just like your mother.
Aunty. / Yes, I'm your aunty.
Suwo.
I'll wait outside.
Be careful.
Uncle...
Van Trach probably
knows we're here.
We should go. / Yes.
We still have a
chance to kill him.
To avenge our parents. /
Your father was a warrior
but he fought for justice.
He would never let
his sons waste their live
for the sake of vengeance.
Have you forgotten? That day,
father set out to negotiate peace
but instead he was murdered.
Jamar, don't.
I won't be so foolish
to make the mistake.
Revenge is a right.
He robbed us of our family.
Revenge may be a right
but forgiveness
makes you stronger.
Jamar.
I'm wrong.
Your father never
acted out of hatred.
He always chose
to forgive, if he could.
If not for revenge,
then why are we here?
To serve justice.
For our people.
Jamar...
Halo.
Van Trach.
Aku melihat ada
reunian keluarga.
Kiona.
Pasti kalian lagi berbahagia.
Aku merasa agak lancang
bila aku tak ikut gabung
ke dalam perayaan reuni...
mengingat betapa
banyaknya... / Hey
keluarga kita sebenarnya.
Maksudku, selama 20
tahun terakhir istrimu
telah tidur denganku, Arana.
Banyak malam indah kuhabiskan
untuk memahami kesenangannya
dan penderitaannya.
Lepaskan istriku, Arana...
dan akan kubiarkan kalian
semua mati secara terhormat.
We're surrounded.
To die with you
would be my
greatest honor, Arana.
Bakar rumah itu!
Biar dia keluar.
Tembak mereka semua.
Semuanya.
Let me go.
Seruni?
Dia telah membuat pilihan.
Dia akan terbakar
bersama mereka semua.
Animals! Get back.
Stay down.
Suwo.
Everyone all right?
Uncle!
Arana.
Jamar, we can use
the smoke to escape.
What? / Clear the way first.
Are you mad? /
You clear the way.
I'll help uncle.
No way, we have
to stay as a group.
Please trust me. I will
bring them out in one piece.
Berjanjilah, kau akan
keluarkan mereka.
Kami berada di belakangmu.
Percayalah.
Ayo!
Cepat!
Uncle, we need to
cover your wound.
Bear with it, Uncle. /
It's just a scratch, Suwo.
Just bear with the
pain for a while.
Suwo,
our time together is at an end.
No. / It is time
for you to take hold
of your own destiny.
I'm not leaving you two behind.
Indeed you aren't
because I'm the
one who has to leave.
I have always loved you
and Jamar
as my own sons.
Your father will be so
proud of both of you.
I'm sure that's what he'll said
when the wind
carries me to meet him.
Don't worry, Suwo.
I'm very much at peace.
It is time for you to leave now.
Jamar is waiting for you.
Go.
Dimana mereka?
/ Mereka tak ikut.
Apa maksudmu?
Mereka sudah tiada.
Kau menyuruhku...
untuk pergi duluan...
dan kalian akan
berada di belakangku.
Aku sudah berusaha. / Kau
suruh aku mempercayaimu.
Katakan sesuatu!
Ini tak adil. / Adil?
Kau mau tahu apa
itu ketidakadilan?
Paman mati gara-gara dirimu.
Kau meninggalkan
paman untuk mati.
Masa bodoh!
Hanya dirimulah
satu-satunya keluargaku.
Maaf.
Paman menyuruhku menyampaikan
pesan bahwa dia menyesal.
Sekarang dia pasti
sedang mengawasi kita
bersama ayah.
Dan apapun rencana
kita selanjutnya...
kita lakukan demi rakyat.
Rakyat kita.
Come on. Go.
Go!
Kami tak menemukan mayat mereka.
Pikiranmu apa sama denganku?
Aku mulai bosan
melihat orang digantung.
Itu kelamaan.
Cowok-cowokmu akan terlambat.
Sir, our guests have arrive.
Yah, apes aku.
Dan tepat waktu.
Tutup gerbangnya!
Tembak mati mereka.
Kau siap? / Selalu siap.
Kurasa mereka ingin
berhadapan langsung.
Van Trach, let's make a deal.
Kesepakatan?
Take your men, leave this place
and don't ever return.
Seperti yang kalian lihat, kami
semua cukup nyaman disini.
Oh?
In that case, be prepared
to face judgement.
Memang siapa kalian?
Cowboy dari Tanah Barat?
Cowboys mengendarai kuda
bukan kerbau.
Dan jika aku tak bisa
sebut kalian Cowboys
maka kupanggil saja
kalian Buffalo Boys.
So what's it going to be...
war or peace?
Kurasa ini yang
mereka sebut berunding.
Tembakkan meriam!
Suwo!
Jamar!
Jamar, tidak, tidak, tidak.
Hm.
I'll give you one bullet.
What are you going to do?
Kalian cuma cari mampus
kemari.
Kau tangguh juga, brengsek.
Are you ready?
All ready.
Hey.
Uncle was right. This
dagger saved my life.
Look, this is where
the bullet bounced off it.
I'll get the horses ready.
I know that you must leave.
So must we.
They will be back
for more blood.
We'll meet again
when the time is right.
Tell the rest of our people
that there's still hope.
And there are still people
who are willing to fight
for justice.
Hey.
This belong to my uncle.
Arana.
And now it's yours.
Take care of it, yeah.
Yes.
Thank you.
We'll never forget you.
Hm.
We'll meet them again.
What?
How are you so sure?
Because when the
legends are born
they will never die.
Prediksi Togel Jitu, Terbukti JP tiap hari
aplikasi android bit.ly/togelandroid