For hundreds of years,
fishermen have shared tales of a
mythical shark off the Baja coast.
One of godlike proportions,
driving men to
the brink of insanity
with visions of death.
To my people, it is known by
the name"El Demonio Negro."
Legend says it only
comes when summoned.
Nacho...
Nacho?
Nacho, check.
♪ Everybody wants
Just a little redemption♪
♪ Everybody needs
Just a little affection♪
♪ Everybody hurts
Everybody heals♪
Smell that. Ah, so good.
Argh! Tell me lad,
have ye spotted any
pirate ships off the coast?
That'’s a negative, Captain,
but I think we'’re getting close.
Hey bud, you wanna hit us with
another of those trivia questions?
Yeah, let'’s do that again.
Okay...
- Fun fact 32.
- Oh, God.
Hey. Stop it.
Most prominent species of fish
along the Baja peninsula?
Ooh, wait. I think
I know this one.
Honey, are there
any easy questions?
Or even better, how about
we play something else?
I'’m already sick of this place
and we'’re not even there yet.
Salmon. Salmon. Come
on. Salmon. Salmon.
I know that there'’s
no salmon in the Baja.
I'’ll say a dorkfish.
Hey Tommy, is it a dorkfish?
Maybe... or could be
a red-lipped batfish!
- Oh, could it?
- Yes, it could.
Yellowfin tuna. Yellowfin
tuna. Final answer.
Striped marlin. Duh.
Duh.
Duh? Duh?
What, are you getting
snippy with us, pal?
So he'’s allowed to say "duh"?
I used to get in trouble
for that. Audrey--
Nobody'’s allowed to
say "duh."That'’s so unfair.
Baby, baby... I
don'’t like "duh."
You guys are picking
favorites. Unbelievable.
I can'’t believe it. Calm down.
- It'’s rude.
- Unbelievable, you guys.
♪ A beautiful day ♪
♪ Freedom, freedom ♪
♪ Freedom for a change ♪
Actually, Mr. Fun Fact,
Bahia was our first getaway as
a couple before we were married.
Yes, it was.
Whoa, I'’m gonna yak.
Your daddy was so
romantic back then.
- I still am.
- No, you'’re not.
How long ago was that?
Well, your sister just turned
15, so it was 15 years ago.
And nine months.
Exactly.
Ew!
You were quite a
shock to us too, sweetie.
Oh, I feel so special now.
Hey, hey, hey. You are special.
Wait, what?
Anyway...
Bahia was where I landed my
first installation gig with Nixon Oil.
Boring.
No, it'’s not boring,
because after that...
...financially, I knew
that I would be able
to support a family
and marry the woman that I love.
You mean, marry the
woman you got pregnant?
- Oh, burn!
- Hey, yeah, stop it!
- Endless.
- Stop it. Yeah.
- Why do we have kids?
- I have no idea.
I just hope we
get to see pirates.
Pirates are lame, Tommy.
You'’re one to talk.
The only pirate you know is the
one on the bottle of Captain Morgan.
- Shut up, Tommy!
- Tommy!
- Audrey!
- That'’s not true!
- Let'’s hope so.
- What do you mean by that?
- What does he mean by that?
- Tommy... He'’s lying.
You'’re only 15. What do you
know about Captain Morgan?
You'’re such a liar, Tommy.
Dad, I think I
see it. Is that it?
Yep, buddy. That'’s
her. El Diamante.
Are you gonna decompose it?
Decommission, genius.
I don'’t know, buddy.
It all depends on if
she passes, you know,
safety measures, system
functionality, refinery quotas.
Oh, do you want him - to try that again in English?
- Oh, Audrey.
I will only decommission
a rig like El Diamante
if we can'’t resuscitate
her. It'’s kind of like--
Pulling the plug.
Dad should decommission you!
And I should pull your plug!
No, you wouldn'’t.
Shut up.
Hey, were you able
to get an ocean view?
Paul... You did book, right?
Baby, that hotel'’s
never gonna be full.
Ooh, Dad'’s in trouble. Tommy...
Hey, I don'’t know. I just thought it
would be nice to stay at that same place.
Hey, uh, where is this anyway?
Costa Azul. Nicest
hotel in town.
They make a mean callo
de hacha. Aye verdad.
Pair it with a cold margarita
and you got yourself a happy wife.
I want nachos.
You know, actually, I think there was a
good little hotel restaurant right up here.
Yeah, Dad. Looks
amazing. Great choice.
I wonder what
happened to it? Mmm.
Uh-huh. Nicest hotel
in town? Really, Dad?
A lot has changed since
the last time we were here.
It definitely ain'’t full.
No kidding. I guess I should
have called, huh? Yeah.
Senor, hello. Uh, excuse
me. Do you speak English?
Sir, do you speak English?
He doesn'’t speak English.
No?
De hecho, he doesn'’t
speak anything at all.
You'’re a long way
from home, gringo.
Man, I'’m just down here
for a weekend with my family.
Families don'’t just come
here for the weekend.
Yes.
Yeah, I work for Nixon Oil.
I'’m sure you'’ve heard of us.
I mean, we practically
built this place.
Take a look around, cabrón.
Proud of your work?
Audrey y Tommy.
Please?
I'’ll call for the kids.
Whoa.
What is it?
Who cares? Just keep walking.
I never noticed it before.
Tlaloc. The Aztec god.
Why is it here?
Where'’s Tommy?
Tommy. Tommy.
Come on. Honey.
Honey.
Tommy.
Come on. You gotta stay with us.
Gracias.
Oh, by the way, back there
when you said... protection.
What'’d you mean?
Protection from what?
El Demonio.
El Demonio? The Demon?
Wait! Senor El Rey!
This for you.
That was a very
nice thing to do.
God, I can'’t believe you'’d
share your pirate patch with him.
That'’s fantastic.
Muchas gracias.
No, no, no. I-- I
get it. It'’s the boss.
All right, I will
head out there now.
Okay, I understand. I got it.
- All right, bye.
- Okay, guys.
We'’re gonna have to
figure out something else
because we'’re not gonna
stay in this town. Aw, man.
Who was that, honey?
The company.
For some reason, they'’re on my back
to get this inspection done immediately.
NRT is up our ass.
So, look, I'’ll ferry out to the
Diamante, I'’ll do the inspection.
While I'’m out there,
you book us someplace else in
Ensenada, someplace nice. Okay?
- Yeah.
- I'’ll be back before sunset.
And you'’re leaving us here?
Here?
What are we supposed
to do in the meantime?
Oh, what are we supposed
Oh, my-- No, no, no, no.
Guys... Don'’t.
Guys.
I will only be gone
a few hours, okay?
Are you sure about this, honey?
The sooner I go, the sooner
we can get out of this place.
And how are you gonna get there?
Uh, the company says I got a boat
waitin'’ for me down in the harbor.
Cool. Can I go with you?
No.
Sorry, little man, you are not
quite tall enough for this ride.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
- Trust me. Okay?
- Mmm.
Besides, Mom, I'’m pretty
sure people around here
have bigger problems
than worrying about us.
Really?
What is that supposed to mean?
"Taloc."
T-la-la-loc.
It'’s Tlaloc, guys.
- Yeah.
- It'’s not that hard.
The creepy god
painted everywhere?
Maybe that'’s why the
villagers are so quiet.
That is just part
of their culture.
And besides, little man,
pirates back in the day
did not have Internet,
so why don'’t we put
this away for a while
and you try being a real
pirate. Sí... That'’s a great idea.
Aye, aye, Captain.
I'’ll consider it.
Hmm. Yeah, we'’re
gonna be fine. But hurry.
- Bye, Dad.
- Be nice.
Fine. Okay.
In the meantime, we are
going to enjoy the view. Hmm?
You speak English?
A little.
Do me a favor.
Keep an eye on my
family for me, would you?
Gracias.
Audrey, it'’s only-- Can I?
No. - I'’ll give it to you later.
- Okay, fine.
Hola. Buenos días.
Uh, my name is
Paul. Paul Sturges.
I'’m with, um-- - I'’m with Nixon Oil.
- Ah! Sí.
I'’m supposed to ferry
out to the rig from here?
Yes. Uh, Choco'’s at the shore.
Waiting for you. Right there.
Right. Uh, hey, do me a favor.
Radio out to the rig, - let '’em know I'’m on my way.
- Absolutely.
Gracias. Gracias.
Welcome.
Hola!
Hola, amigo!
Paul Sturges. Nixon Oil.
Yeah, I think you took me out
to the rig a few years ago. Right?
Sí, señor. Let'’s get going.
I want to get back
before sunset.
Okay.
- Got it?
- I'’m waiting for the wave.
So, what happened here?
What do you mean, sir?
What do I mean? I mean...
where are all the boats?
Where'’d all the fishermen go?
Where'’d all the people
who live here go?
Things...
very bad, sir.
What-- What do you
mean, things are very bad?
El Diamante...
El Demonio.
The Demon.
Okay.
Hey, I'’m confused. Why
are we stopping again?
Sorry, sir.
I can'’t go past here.
Why not?
Bad vibes.
- Bad vibes?
- Yeah.
Look, Cho-- Choco, if
it'’s more money you need,
- I got money.
- No, no, sir.
I-- I can'’t.
But the boat'’s ready.
I check everything.
Engine is strong like a bull.
Look.
See? Pepe is waiting
for you on the rig.
Yeah, I know Pepe.
He knows everything.
He'’s a good man.
You call when ready.
You know there'’s no
cell service out here, right?
Sí, but you call on radio.
Forget it. I'’ll-- I'’ll
get myself back.
Thanks for nothing.
You'’re welcome.
"'’Taloc'’ is the god of rain.
His name means
the nectar of the earth.
He'’s one of the oldest and most
formidable gods of the Aztec pantheon,
dating back 2,500 years ago.
He was the benevolent
giver of life and water.
But he was also greatly feared.
He could stop the rain and
provoke drought and hunger.
He could hurl the
lightning upon the earth
and unleash
devastating hurricanes.
They even named a
mountain after '’Taloc.'’"
It'’s Tlaloc, baby.
Something'’s off.
What is it that I'’m
not getting here?
There'’s no birds.
"He was the ruler
of the third sun,"
and this other guy whose name
I won'’t even try to pronounce
stole his girlfriend.
"Then afterwards,
he became so angry
that he ignored
everyone'’s prayers for rain."
Wicked.
No. Jerk move.
Kinda like how Ross
cheated on Rachel.
He didn'’t cheat on
her. They were on break.
I need to use the bathroom.
Make it quick, okay?
Boy, that kid'’s impressionable.
Are you fighting because
of Rachel and Ross?
Ah, okay, enough of this.
Ugh, can you do it? All right.
Mom?
Audrey! Behind me!
Come.
Tommy! Here.
- Stay here.
- Stay with me. Tommy. Here.
Run!
Uh, Mom?
Audrey? Audrey, run!
Mom? Mom, I think
we'’re being followed.
Ignore them, Audrey. No one
is allowed to assault you ever.
Not even disrespect you,
okay? And that goes for you, too.
I'’m gonna get us
out of here. I promise.
Sí, El Diamante.
Mom?
Mom!
I got this, baby, okay?
Muchas gracias. Thank you.
Jesus, where is everyone?
Hello?
Pepe?
Anybody?
What the hell is this?
Hey, Pepe!
Corporate'’s not
gonna go for this.
Hello?
Pepe!
Hola, Pepe!
Hello? Pepe?
Pepe.
Is there anyone here?
Pepe?
Aw, hey, girl, you
here all alone?
No, señor. No, he'’s not.
Take it easy with that.
I'’m just looking for Pepe.
Pepe is dead.
Who are you cabrón?
My name is Paul Sturges.
I'’m-- I'’m with Nixon Oil.
What'’s going on here?
Didn'’t the harbor master tell
you guys I was on my way?
No.
Our radio is dead.
I never thought I'’d see a
guy from the company again.
I-- I-- I'’m just here
to do the inspection.
- Oh, is that right?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Little late, huh, guero?
You alone?
Yeah. Yeah, of
course I'’m alone.
Where the hell is everyone?
- How'’d you get here?
- Shh.
The-- The little motorboat.
Chinga.
Chinga? Chinga what?
A family? Let me see.
Yes, what the hell?
Hey, Tommy, get away
from the edge, okay?
Mom, what'’s that?
Did you not hear me?
Mom?
What are you doing?
What-- Why are you
doing that? Stop doing that!
What the--
There'’s Dad and
some other guys.
Is he?
What is happening?
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Mom, what'’s going on?
- I don'’t know, baby. But hold tight. Hold tight!
Where is that coming from?
- That'’s where!
- What?
Whoa!
Are you okay, guys? Keep
your hands in the boat.
Go with Daddy. Go with Daddy.
What'’s happening, babe?
Babe, what are you
doing? Why are you here?
What is that?
Pa?
- Why are you here?
- We couldn'’t stay there, okay?
There were-- were. The body!
There'’s bodies! All of them dead!
There are-- there were-- Hey,
hey. There'’s nothing there.
- There'’s nothing there.
- Just breathe.
But there were-- But I
saw--Baby, you'’re fine.
- Just breathe.
- But I saw all of them.
It'’s just oil. It'’s okay.
All right, let'’s get her
cleaned up and dried off.
You'’re okay.
- You'’re okay. - Got her?
- Here, Tommy.
- Lets get you dry.
Get you dry and
cleaned up, okay?
I'’ll be right there
with you, okay?
- What is happening here?
- What'’s happening?
- What made the boat sink?
- Why did he leave?
- What is going on?
- What did she see?
- What did she see, huh?
- You don'’t wanna know.
- No, we do wanna know. What'’s happening?
What is it?
What is that?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Jesus Christ.
No.
The Black Demon.
Where are my kids?
Gracias.
Hey. Careful, it'’s hot.
Baby, here.
Hey, I wasn'’t mad at
you back there, okay?
Don'’t try to
understand it, guero.
Just accept that
it'’s real and alive.
How long has that
thing been out there?
I don'’t know.
I'’ve lost track of time.
Me llamo Chato.
Chato.
And where'’s the
rest of the crew?
Gone. Some managed to evacuate.
Others, not so lucky.
Me and Junior, we were the
only ones smart enough to stay.
Smart enough?
Paul?
I-- I-- I can'’t get any signal.
There'’s no signal.
There'’s no service.
What'’s going on?
What'’s that thing we saw?
I don'’t know.
Oh, that poor man.
I ask him to come here
and I treat him like shit.
No, no, baby. Hey,
listen to me. Listen to me.
It'’s not your fault. You couldn'’t
have known. None of us could.
What is that then?
Some kind of shark.
It'’s not a shark.
It'’s a megalodon.
Those don'’t exist.
Guys, I told you to stay inside.
What are you doing here?
Hey, look. There must be
some other way off this rig.
Do you think we'’d
be here if there was?
Radio stopped working weeks
ago. Our calls went ignored.
- Ignored?
- Ignored? What do you mean?
What-- What about - the satellite phone?
- It was taken with the crew.
Look. If you'’re gonna ask
me questions about boats,
phones or some other way
of getting off this damn rig,
then we'’re gonna be
here for a long time.
Who'’s this little guy?
That'’s Toro.
Tough name for a little dog.
Don'’t look him in the eye then.
What? Do you
think I made that up?
Guess he'’s not that
tough after all, huh?
What was that?
That'’s coming from
the southern leg.
It'’s trying to
bring the rig down.
The southern leg
holds the auxiliary line.
Ines, get the kids downstairs
and inside, all right?
I'’m going to - figure this out.
- Okay.
Where? We'’re going inside.
What exactly are
your jobs on the rig?
I do whatever is needed.
Me and my carnal are trying to keep this
hunk of shit from falling into the ocean.
Hunk of shit is
putting it mildly.
All right, give me a complete
rundown on Diamante.
Control room, electrical,
standard satellite, the whole thing.
Rundown? Nothing
works. That'’s your rundown.
Nothing works.
And how often does
this thing hit the rig?
El Demonio attacks
when it wants.
- What about the volume?
- Zero.
Spillage has been nonstop - for the past few months.
- Zero?
Are you shitting me? This thing
has been leaking this bad for months?
All those pendejos at
Nixon Oil knew all about it.
We just wondered why you guys
never sent the resources to fix it.
That'’s absurd.
Does all this damage look
absurd to you, guero? Huh?
Let me tell you something.
We grew up here.
So when we heard about
all these pinches problemas
this place was having,
we transferred back.
To see all this? No.
I'’m sorry, man.
If we live through this,
I'’m gonna gather up all of
them bigwig son of a bitches
and feed their huevos to Toro.
Jesus.
Yeah, support'’s been fractured.
I don'’t think it can take
much more punishment.
No, it'’s fine. She'’s designed
to withstand a category five.
Does that feel like a
category five, guero?
The auxiliary is still working.
There goes the auxiliary.
Chinga.
What now?
We need power.
Without the auxiliary line, the
backup generator won'’t work.
Where is it? This line.
This line. This line here.
Then I can repair and reroute
the radio, and we can call for help.
You mean dive?
Is the dive bell
still functional?
- Simón.
- Yeah?
Dad. Carnaroni?
Yeah, bud. That'’s
what they eat down here.
Well, they'’re not my
abuelita'’s enchiladas, but...
...they'’ll keep you full.
Hey, we'’re much
better, verdad, mi amor?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
So, listen. I think I found a way to
fix the radio and get us out of here.
- What?
- Okay.
- So, we have a plan, right?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Why don'’t we open this window so we
can lighten up this place? Help me there.
If the auxiliary line
can be repaired,
we'’re gonna have to do
some work down there.
You know how to weld?
A-- A bit. Yeah.
A bit? It'’s okay.
We'’ll go down. You stay up top.
We'’ll be faster.
I'’ll prep the-- the tanks.
All right, so I'’ll retract
you down in the bell.
You fix the line.
Hey, wait. You aren'’t
actually going down there?
Did you just forget about
the 70-ton shark out there?
Babe, the bell on this rig is
made of thick fine-grained steel.
I'’d like to see that son
of a bitch bite down on it.
- It'’ll be fine.
- Paul...
It'’ll be fine. Hey, kids.
There'’s a chess board,
some books and games.
If you want to use them--
We are not exactly trying
to get comfortable here!
I'’m sorry, I--
So-- Actually--
Actually, it'’s a great idea.
Why would a shark be
so interested in an oil rig?
Well...
your company...
this rig, was to provide jobs.
A better future for Bahia Azul.
And it did, at first,
until regulation standards started
getting more and more overlooked.
Nobody gave a shit. Nobody.
You know, this is
not just any shark.
Not just a megalodon.
What is it then?
It'’s much more than that.
It'’s a curse.
Curse? Come on, man.
Now'’s not the time for this.
Paul, let him talk. Please.
El Demonio is an extension.
It'’s the vengeance
of an old god.
You know, when I was a-- a boy,
my abuelito would always tell
me stories about the god of rain.
"Taloc."
Tlaloc.
Hey, baby, ven.
Mi abuelito would
always remind me
that Tlaloc was
not just any god.
He was a giver of life.
That his tears made the
oceans, the lakes, ríos.
And that most importantly,
we only prayed for
what was needed.
Never more.
Thousands of years
ago, that was not the case.
A great flood came through.
A flood brought
on not by nature,
but by wrath.
Wrath?
You know, people took too much.
They chopped down all the trees.
Instead of just taking
what they needed to eat,
they killed-- they
killed all the animals.
And they tried to control
the rivers and the lakes.
They thought they
were in control.
We thought we were the gods.
That'’s what pissed him off.
And Tlaloc'’s
warning went ignored.
Until El Demonio Negro was born.
Here we go.
Brought out of extinction
by Tlaloc himself.
You see, that was
no ordinary meg.
Makes you see things,
plays games with your mind.
Please. You don'’t believe me?
Let'’s ask your daughter
what she saw. Let'’s ask her.
Hey. Hey, hey.
What did you see, Paul?
We are destroying
Tlaloc'’s world.
And now the demon has
come back to protect it.
How are we gonna stop it?
The only way to
stop it is to kill it.
But killing the demon
is not gonna stop Tlaloc.
He'’s gonna keep
getting his revenge
until an ultimate
sacrifice has been made.
Now, you'’ve seen it.
This entire place
is a wasteland.
And everything that
was sacred or gave us life
has been killed.
It'’s "Taloc."
That'’s why it was so
dusty back in Bahia.
"Taloc" won'’t let it rain.
It'’s Tla-loc.
Tla... loc.
Tla...
Ta... Tla...
Ta... T-la...
Tla...
- Loc.
- Tlaloc.
What'’s that?
Hmm.
Gracias.
Tlaloc. Tlaloc.
Enough! So, that'’s your answer?
Everything that'’s gone wrong - with this world?
- Paul...
No, no, no. Come on, man.
Angry gods? Ultimate sacrifice?
- Paul, will you please stop?
- No. No. No.
I'’m not gonna sit
here and listen to him
fill our children'’s heads
with superstitious nonsense.
They have enough to worry
about as it is, for Chrissake.
Open your eyes, cabrón.
We are destroying
our own planet.
We gotta do this
now. We gotta do this.
Hey.
No, no, no, no, no. Don'’t you--
Do not listen to
what he'’s saying.
He'’s gone crazy.
Are you sure about that?
Baby, we can'’t exactly
deny what we'’re dealing with.
There is a giant shark
out there, and you saw it!
Paul...
Bell'’s on battery!
What do you think? Lowering it manually
should make it much brighter down below.
So, you do believe it'’s Tlaloc?
No. But I know a big-ass
shark when I see one.
He really seems
to like you, guero.
Always making noise
when you'’re around.
Funny. Ha-ha.
Remember. The intake
valves are 200 feet down.
No, no. Más.
Seventy-five meters.
Do those comms work?
No. But we have cameras.
You can watch us with this.
We'’ll signal you when we stop.
All right.
A little bit. A
little bit. A little bit.
I hear you, tough guy.
What is that?
Come on!
Stay put. What happened?
Hey.
Chato!
Where'’s Junior?
- Where'’s Junior? - Are you okay?
- Where'’s Junior? Where is he?
- Where is Junior? What happened?
- Help him out! Help him out!
- Junior!
Hermano. Junior!
- Help him out! Help him out!
- Junior!
Help him out! Help him out!
Oh, my God! Junior!
Junior!
What?
What'’s wrong, Audrey?
No, nothing.
Just another one of
Mom and Dad'’s fights.
Oh, God.
Junior.
You will not take my
family away from me.
He didn'’t deserve
to die like that, Paul.
He-- He was--
He was trying to save us.
He-- He didn'’t deserve
to die like that. He--
He didn'’t deserve that.
Baby...
Honey, can I say?
Everything is
gonna be all right.
You keep telling me that, Paul.
But it'’s not.
It'’s not all right.
Hey, Paul. Hey, I'’m not--
I'’m not asking you to be completely
invested in what he'’s saying,
but you can'’t tell me
this is normal. Come on.
How does that help you?
I don'’t know! But there'’s some
things that we can'’t explain.
I just need you to acknowledge
that, at least while we'’re here.
Here? You are not
supposed to be here!
I specifically told you to wait with
the kids and you blatantly ignored me!
You'’re right. You'’re right.
I'’m sorry. I'’m sorry.
I'’m so sorry.
But I just couldn'’t stay there with
those drunks and Santa Muerte cult!
I couldn'’t! I couldn'’t!
And you told me it would
last just a couple of hours tops!
I... I thought it would be.
I did. I really
thought it would be.
I'’m sorry.
I know, I know you'’re scared.
It'’s not just us.
The kids.
Baby, if something
were to happen to them,
I don'’t know what I would do.
I am working on it.
I promise you, - I am working on it.
- Okay.
Are you guys done arguing yet?
Hey, hey.
No, no, no. We--
We weren'’t arguing.
What'’s this?
- Coffee.
- Coffee for me?
Oh, thank you.
I need to go check on Toro.
Oh, by the way, where'’s Junior?
He'’s in the electrical room.
He'’ll be back soon, Tommy.
Okay.
New shirt?
Junior gave me that shirt.
Shit.
Can'’t wear it right now.
I'’m sorry, man.
I'’m sorry about your partner.
He gave me ten
years of his life.
Met him down south
in a rig when he was 20.
He never complained.
He always did what
I asked him to do.
Did you see it?
I did.
It'’s enough
firepower to flatten...
Why?
How much time do we have?
I don'’t know.
Hey, look. Hey! Hey!
Over here! Over here! - Get your gun!
- What'’s going on? No.
- No!
- Get your flare gun! Where is it?
There'’s nothing there!
- No! Give me that!
- What are you doing?
The ship is right
there! Don'’t you see it?
Right there, look! Mira!
- Look! Look!
- There'’s nothing out there!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
It makes you see things!
It plays games with your mind.
The only cabrónes we
can rely on right now...
El Demonio, this spill.
This is Mother Nature
holding us accountable.
This is our problem.
The spill?
The hell with the spill.
It'’s not my fault.
I'’m not God.
- No.
- I didn'’t create that thing out there.
You'’re not God.
More like a pinche puppet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, man.
We'’re all puppets
in the end of the day.
The company'’s puppet, pendejo!
You think God cares
about this shiny watch?
Or your SUVs?
Or this pretty red shirt?
Hey, I paid my dues,
pal. I earned all this.
So you can just take your superstitious
Aztec bullshit and shove it up your ass,
because I'’m not about
to lose any of it, ever!
And this is burgundy!
You have no idea what you have!
Right?
- Okay, let'’s do it, man!
- Stop it! Stop it! What'’s going on here?
I'’ll tell you what'’s going on.
This.
All of this.
It'’s just...
It'’s just incompetence.
It'’s negligence.
It'’s mismanagement.
That'’s what it is.
And that thing
out there is just a--
a mutant freak from all of it!
Tommy.
I'’m not hungry.
You need to eat.
- Hey, uh, food?
- Uh, what is that?
Uh, veggie lasagna. You want?
No. Give it to Toro.
Are we leaving now?
Yeah, but, uh-- but Dad'’s
got some work to do first.
Got it?
- Dad?
- Yeah?
What happened to your mouth?
- What?
- Your mouth.
Oh. I, uh, slipped on the deck.
Are we gonna die, Dad?
What, baby?
- Hey, hey.
- Hey.
No. Hey, buddy.
What kind of a question is
that? No, no, no. Listen to me.
Sometimes life just
gives us problems
that are bigger than
we think we can handle.
We just need to focus and
take our time and figure it out.
Kind of like chess, you know.
With a king and his army.
- Right, Dad? - Exactly, mi amor.
And all of the pieces need to
work together in order to win.
Yeah, but sacrifices need to
be made to protect the king.
Hey, what?
In Tlaloc'’s case,
he preferred children,
and it was the tears of children
that created the rivers and waterways.
Waterways.
You think that'’s
gonna happen to you?
The Aztecs would
literally rip the fingernails
out of their kids just
to get them crying
right before
slitting their throats.
Hey, hey. Buddy, buddy.
Listen to me. There'’ll be
no sacrificing today. Okay?
Yes, Dad.
And when you come
back, we can leave?
Exactly. That'’s what
I'’m trying to figure out.
Hey, hey, listen. You
guys want to help?
Yeah. What?
Okay. So, look around and
find anything that you can
that might help
us get off this rig.
Like what?
I-I don'’t know. You'’re
smart. You'’ll figure it out.
Okay.
Waterways.
Hey, bud.
Wanna help your sister? Huh?
Oh, mi amor. Mmm.
I don'’t want you to
worry about a thing, okay?
I'’ll be right back.
Paul?
Paul.
Hey. Baby.
Hey, come on. You
can'’t do this by yourself.
Why the hell not?
If this is teamwork,
let him help you.
What, so he can slap
the shit out of me again?
Paul!
You want to tell me
what you'’re doing?
I have a new plan.
We'’ve been over this.
I'’ve shown you every
blueprint I can find.
What are you looking for?
- Waterways.
- What?
- Waterways?
Yeah.
Okay, the generator.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. The drain.
Where'’s the drain?
The drain? Okay.
If I can reroute
the cooling system,
I can get the generator to work.
Okay, guero. Okay.
Maybe we can fix the radio.
It'’s stuck.
And now what?
Well, you weld, right?
Mr. Chato.
Me.
Tommy, did you find anything?
Audrey.
Mommy.
Daddy.
And Tlaloc.
Tommy, did you find any--
Tommy?
Lord of the sea,
grant us humble passage
through your turbulent sea.
Forgive us, Tlaloc.
Tommy? Listo.
I don'’t know if this works.
- Tommy?
Tommy!
Help, Audrey!
- Where is he?
- I don'’t know. I thought he was with you!
- No. Tommy? Tommy!
- Help, Mommy! Help!
Ines! Ines!
Mom! Mom, help!
- Okay.
- Hey! Hey!
- Hey, Mom!
- Audrey!
Hey!
Here it comes, guero!
Come on! Come on!
Go, Tommy! Go, go!
Vamos! Vamos! Vamos! Vamos!
How'’s my little pirate?
I'’ll take over. You go
ahead and get cleaned up.
Hey, hey, what'’s-- - what'’s wrong? What is it?
- Nothing.
Baby, I think I got
something figured out.
- I just need a little time.
- You ignored all the warnings, Paul.
What? What warnings?
What'’re you talking about?
I saw your signatures.
My signatures?
You'’re gonna deny it now?
Deny what? Honey, I don'’t
know what you'’re talking about.
You could'’ve prevented
this from happening.
Prevent what? Honey, I don'’t
know what you'’re talking about.
I saw your signatures
on the safety report.
You want to explain?
Huh?
- It'’s complicated.
- No, no, no. Don'’t give me that bullshit.
It is--Don'’t give me
that bullshit. Don'’t.
What'’s going on, Mom?
Listen to me.
Ines, don'’t do this.
Not right now. Mom?
Listen to me. We can talk
about it when we get out of here.
- They should know.
- What? No.
So they'’ll never do
something like this.
- Ines, please, baby, please.
- Tell them. Tell them.
Tell them you'’ve been signing off
on this monstrosity for all these years.
- Dad?
- Haven'’t you?
Okay, I-I did it.
I did it. There. Is that
what you want to hear?
Please, let'’s just not - talk about this right now.
- Why?
Because we can talk - about it later.
- Because it'’s my job.
- No, it'’s not your job!
It'’s not your job!
Your job is to shut
places like this down!
Do you have any idea
what you'’ve done? Huh?
To us? To...
Look around you, Paul.
People are dying
because of this.
- Dying.
- I had no choice.
I didn'’t.
I did it for us. - I did it for them.
- They lost everything.
I did it so that we
could have a better life.
- I had no choice!
- At the cost of other people'’s lives?
No, you did have a
choice! You did! You did!
You...
You did it for yourself, Paul.
You are the monster.
Not that thing out there.
We'’re not gonna
make it, are we?
No, señor.
First time I inspected Diamante,
it was my first year on the job.
She was beautiful.
Because she was built
just outside of
federal jurisdiction,
and the administration just
rolled back all those regulations.
Companies like Nixon Oil...
they were able to come
down to places like this
and implement their own
self-inspection procedures.
In that very first
test, she just...
she failed miserably.
I hoped that over
time, I'’d be able to
help make improvements to her.
So, when I got back to shore,
I, uh-- I drafted my report.
I included all
Diamante'’s hazards or...
or shortcomings.
And I turned it in.
The very next morning,
they called me into
this very fancy office.
They asked me if
I liked my new job,
if my soon-to-be-wife and I
were settling into the new house.
And they tossed-- tossed
the report back at me.
Right then and
there, they started
"suggesting"
that I overlook some of
the problems with the rig.
They insinuate...
that if I don'’t do it,
they'’ll find somebody who will.
I revised my report.
I signed off on every
report that they gave me.
This went on and on for years.
All so some rich oil men up
north could keep raking it in
while this little village
was laid to waste.
I mean, I played my part,
but I had no idea
it got this bad.
You see that bomb?
Those charges are
the same ones we used
for underwater demolition.
Bastards I worked for are
the same ones trying to kill me.
I knew who you were as
soon as I heard your name.
Eh?
I just didn'’t know Nixon Oil
was trying to blow your ass up.
God.
Oh, it makes perfect sense.
They'’re my signatures
on the documents.
They get me out of the picture,
they have the perfect scapegoat.
Ayayay, guero.
What makes a measure
of a man is not his house,
dinero,
his clothes.
It'’s what he does in
times of uncertainty.
You'’re about to
lose your family.
And the only question
you gotta ask yourself is,
how do you make it right?
The faster you
figure that out...
the faster you'’ll
know what to do.
And don'’t worry
about the pinche bomba
blowing our asses up.
Hmm.
You'’re making me nervous.
Sorry.
Hey, guys. What about this?
No, no, no, no, no. That
raft'’s no bueno. It has rips.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, Tommy.
Help me open it.
Mayday, Mayday, Mayday.
Somos El Diamante de Nixon Oil.
Mayday...
Mayday, Mayd--
Chingas.
Okay, uh, Tommy, can you
take this to the back, please?
Hey, what are you guys up to?
Oh, Ma. Grab the acetone and
the life jackets from the lockers.
- Please.
- Acetone?
What are we doing?
We need patches. Lots of them.
- Do we have glue?
- Watch and learn.
I knew you'’d
come through, girl.
Here. Uh-huh. Did
you find everything?
Audrey, do you have another one?
- Uh, yeah. How many more?
- Give me one.
And I want two.
Guys, this is really working.
Yeah.
Wait, how long
have you been here?
And you'’re just now
trying to fix the radio?
Truth is,
you didn'’t want anyone
to come here, did you?
You wanted Diamante to
go down the whole time.
Even if it meant
going down with it.
To save your people.
You got a plan, guero?
Hell, yes, I have a plan.
I'’m gonna blow that SOB up.
You can'’t just blow up
that pinche Demonio rig up
and expect
everything to be okay.
Of course not. That'’s why
I'’m gonna seal the leak first.
Stop the leak?
That'’s impossible.
Clearly, you don'’t know
shit about repair valves.
I saw something down there
that only the guys with
expensive red shirts know.
You mean burgundy.
And, in the
process, if I'’m lucky,
I will appease
an angry rain god.
But how?
If I can just manually seal
the repair valve on the drill line.
It'’s a long shot,
but hopefully it will
relieve enough pressure
to trigger the
blowout preventer.
Therefore...
Sealing the well....sealing
the well. Exactly.
Seal the well, I grab the bomb
and I feed it to that son of a bitch.
And then what?
Then I-- I get to the bell.
It should protect
me from the blast.
- What'’s left of it.
- And then you and I,
we get us a really good bottle
of tequila and we get drunk.
You'’re buying.
No. No, you'’re
not--Chato, listen to me.
There'’s no
other--Do not do this.
Yo soy jefe. - You will go down with it.
- Listen to me. Listen to me.
You'’ve got a big heart.
But this rig, this-- this leak,
it'’s my fault.
That thing down
there, it wants me.
You know that. You
of all people know that.
And this will work.
As soon as I go down, you
get my family into that raft...
...and you get them off this
rig and you get them to safety.
Take my bag with you. Okay?
Hey, Dad.
Yeah, buddy?
Does this work?
Wow. It-- It-- Is it done?
Yep.
You okay, Dad?
Yeah, baby, I'’m okay.
Hey.
You guys ready
to get out of here?
It feels like maybe
we should... pray?
You know how to pray?
Wow.
After all these years of me trying
to make you believe in something.
Okay. You finally
made your point.
You too, Mr. Chato.
Paul. Wait, no.
Listen.
I have made terrible
mistakes and I am so sorry.
There is a bomb on the rig.
What?
I-- I don'’t have time
to explain right now.
I actually think it helps us.
I'’m gonna go down,
I'’m gonna dislodge '’em,
and then I'’m gonna get up
inside the bell and drop '’em.
To kill the monster.
That'’s not the
monster, remember?
Baby, my mind is clear.
I love you.
Now, get the kids
to safety. Now. Go.
We'’re out of tanks and
this one'’s almost empty.
I'’ll make it work.
I'’ve been thinkin'’, and if
you don'’t make it, what then?
Then look after my family.
Okay.
You'’re family too, man.
Promise me, whatever
happens down there,
you will get my
family off this rig.
Deal?
You got a deal, cabrón.
If there really is some
pissed-off god out there,
maybe he'’ll cut
us some slack now.
Well, the pinche Demonio won'’t.
I got no spit.
See you on the
other side, amigo.
I love you.
Love you.
All right.
All good.
See you around.
Okay, familia. We gotta go.
Tommy! Watch your step.
Okay. Boy, I'’m
checking out for you.
Vamos. Vamos. Okay.
I'’m ready. Vamos.
I'’m ready.
Nes, are you there? Nes?
Is that Paul?
Paul.
Paul?
Honey, I'’m sorry.
We'’re gonna have to take a rain
check on those margaritas, okay?
No. What are you talking about?
Stick to the plan,
Paul. Stick to the plan.
I'’m afraid this is the plan.
Honey,
tell Chato, his town, his
people, that I'’m sorry.
And things are
gonna get better soon.
No. Get your ass up
here and tell him yourself.
Do you hear me, cabrón?
I left you a gift in my bag.
Make sure it gets
to the right people.
OÓrale, cabrón.
Audrey?
Dad?
Audrey...
my sweet, beautiful young woman.
That'’s your raft.
You had it in you all
along. Remember that.
I will.
Tommy. Yeah, Dad?
Tommy, hey, buddy.
You'’re finally leaving.
It'’s just that...
I'’m not sailing
where you guys are.
I left you a gift
in my bag, okay?
The thing about pirates
is their-- their courage...
their bravery,
their willingness to explore
the world with their crew.
Buddy, you'’re the captain now.
You understand what I'’m saying?
I think so.
- Honey?
- Yeah?
I should'’ve booked.
Don'’t-- Don'’t pull--
Please, don'’t do--
I'’ll check in on you
from time to time.
I love you.
I love you guys.
Hey. Hey.
I love you too.
Okay? I love you too.
Dad!
He did it.
Mom, Mom. Look.
- Look.
- Hey!
Hey, here!
Vamos.
Gracias. Muchas gracias.
Hey.
Daddy'’s always
gonna be with us, okay?
Here.
Mom, it'’s raining.