* Lakukan-jadilah-lakukan-lakukan - lakukan, oh *
Zoey, aku sudah mencintaimu sejak aku melihatmu.
Anda menjatuhkan saya dari kaki saya, ingat?
Saya tahu bahkan saat itu, dan saya pikir Anda juga tahu,
bahwa apa yang kita miliki adalah sesuatu yang istimewa,
sesuatu yang kuat,
sesuatu yang nyata.
Saat aku menatap matamu, aku melihat seluruh hidup kita.
Hari-hari baik, hari-hari buruk,
ulang tahun, hari tua.
I... Aku ingin melakukan semuanya, Zoey!
Selama aku bisa melakukannya denganmu.
Dan tentu saja, itu tidak akan sempurna,
tapi tidak ada di dunia ini yang sempurna,
kecuali kamu.
Saya siap membangun kehidupan,
keluarga, masa depan, bersama,
tapi itu semua dimulai dengan satu pertanyaan.
Zoey...
Uh, siapa nama belakangmu lagi?
Brooks.
Zoey Brooks, maukah kamu menikah denganku?
Apa yang kamu lakukan?
Aku meminta tanganmu.
Kami sudah berkencan dua kali.
Dua kencan sempurna yang ingin saya ubah
menjadi selamanya, jadi, maukah kamu membuatku menjadi yang paling bahagia--
Tidak, tidak, jelas tidak, sama sekali tidak.
Tidak dalam sejuta tahun, tidak!
Yah, mungkin jika Anda mengatakan" ya " sekarang,
dan kemudian kita bisa membicarakannya nanti.
Byron, berdiri.
Ya. Hai.
Kau tahu ini aneh, kan?
Ya, aku tahu ini aneh.
Hanya, saya berusia 30 setengah tahun dan saya tinggal bersama ibu saya,
dan saya penyanyi utama dari band cover Maroon 5.
Saya tidak benar-benar mendapatkan banyak kencan kedua.
Terima kasih atas kejujuranmu, Byron.
Saya yakin ada seseorang di luar sana untuk Anda,
itu bukan aku.
Jadi saya harus pergi.
Ya, itu, eh, itu masuk akal.
Kau akan baik-baik saja?
Oh ya, aku, uh, ya, aku akan baik-baik saja.
Baiklah.
Jadi aku akan meneleponmu?
Tolong jangan.
Oke.
- Selamat! - Selamat!
* Oh, buat aku berakhir *
* Aku semua yang aku inginkan *
* Studi jalan kaki *
* Dalam demonologi *
* Hei, sangat senang kamu bisa berhasil *
* Ya, sekarang kamu benar-benar berhasil *
* Hei, sangat senang kamu bisa melakukannya sekarang *
Anda sedang menonton LOVE: Fully Charged.
Selamat datang di Danau Malibu yang cerah, California,
di mana 12 single seksi akan menghabiskan musim panas
mencari pasangan yang cocok untuk mereka,
dengan hadiah utama cinta sejati
atau mobil.
Musim ini, kami telah mengambil
Coupe Pontiac Solstice tua yang bodoh
dan kami telah mengubahnya
menjadi kendaraan listrik impian Anda.
Dengan jangkauan 300 mil dan kemampuan mengemudi sendiri,
ini adalah LUV-6 yang terisi penuh.
Sekarang kencangkan sabuk pengaman karena minggu ini,
Jordan B. dan Jordyn J.
pergi kencan pertama mereka.
Ada apa?
Saat ini saya mengendarai Ford Fiesta 2009,
tidak ada AC, tidak ada kaca spion,
jadi, Anda tahu saya siap untuk Pontiac itu.
Tapi Jordyn J. terlihat sangat seksi hari ini,
jadi, ya, saya kira kepala saya mulai berputar!
Kamu terlihat sangat seksi hari ini.
- Kau mau anggur? - Ya, terima kasih.
Jadi lihat, mengapa kau memilihku untuk berkencan?
Uh...
Um...
Suruh dia pergi. Cepat, cepat!
Yah, um...
Uh...
Oh, syukurlah.
Misterius...
Karena kamu misterius
dan cantik,
dan kamu menarik perhatianku begitu kamu masuk.
Saya belum merasakan hubungan seperti ini
dengan orang lain di vila,
dan saya senang melihat ke mana perginya ini.
Saya juga senang melihat kemana perginya ini juga.
- Untuk kita. - Untuk kita.
Dan potong!
- Baiklah, itu luka. - Pindah.
Itu bagus, kalian! Hal yang sangat menyenangkan.
Jordyn J., untuk pengakuan dosa.
Hei, bagaimana kabarku?
Oh, berhasil, seperti yang kita latih.
Amerika akan menyayangimu.
Kurasa aku tidak bisa melakukan ini tanpamu.
Bagaimana Anda selalu tahu apa yang harus, seperti, katakan?
Oh, itu hanya bagian dari pekerjaan, Jordan B.
Sekarang, jika Anda permisi, saya harus mendapatkan promosi.
Tangkap mereka, Zo!
Jadi pertanyaan yang saya ajukan kepada Anda,
tim produksi saya yang brilian, adalah ini.
Apakah semua orang melihat apa yang mereka lakukan di Polisi Anjing ?
Ya, itu omong kosong yang aneh.
Aneh, baru...
sial, dan itulah yang aku inginkan darimu untuk pertunjukan kita.
Saya ingin ide-ide baru yang aneh
atau...
kau dipecat.
- Membuat semua orang telanjang? - Tidak!
Bagaimana jika kita memasangkan seseorang dengan hewan?
Kami melakukannya musim lalu!
Bagaimana jika kita mengganti semua gadis dengan ibu mereka?
Itu ide yang luar biasa karena jika ada satu hal
Amerika Tengah suka, itu wanita tua.
Tidak, tidak diuji dengan baik.
Bagaimana jika Jordan B. melamar?
Semuanya diam. Greg, kau punya ide?
Bagaimana jika Jordan B.
diusulkan untuk Jordyn J.?
Sebuah proposal... pada kencan kedua?
Itu adalah shiznit yang aneh,
dan itu sangat jenius, itu hanya bisa berhasil.
Bagaimana Anda datang dengan ini?
Aku tidak tahu!
Aku tahu.
- Karena kau berhubungan denganku. - Sebenarnya, itu ideku!
Oke, jadi alasan saya mengadakan pertemuan ini,
setiap tahun, untuk final,
Saya mengumpulkan tim yang paling cerdas dan terbaik.
Tim yang akan tinggal bersama saya
di situs untuk final kami adalah...
Ini adalah bagaimana Anda melakukan TV.
- Taylor! - Ya!
Brian!
- Aiden. - Ya!
- Rafi! - Ya!
Dan tentu saja, Greg.
Pasti Greg. Semua orang lain... menjadi lebih baik.
Sampai jumpa di atas es. Rapat ditunda.
- Siri, mulai treadmill saya. - Kelley, aku perlu bicara denganmu.
Oke, saya sangat sibuk, jadi cepatlah.
Ini tentang pilihan Anda untuk final langsung.
Saya pikir Anda membuat kesalahan besar.
Merah muda atau merah muda cerah untuk gadis baru?
- Telanjang. - Dia tidak bisa telanjang.
Tidak, tidak, itu warna. Warnanya telanjang.
Apakah saya harus melakukan pekerjaan semua orang di sekitar sini?!
Saya akan menjadi anggota tim yang sangat berharga
karena saya telah mengerjakan acara itu lebih lama dari siapa pun.
- Semua kontestan mempercayai saya. - Tuan Kevyn, pertanyaan dari Legal.
Apakah kita pernah mendapat izin untuk menggunakan Pontiac untuk mobil?
Kami adalah acara nomor satu di jaringan.
Kami tidak bertanya pada Pontiac, kami memberi tahu mereka.
Faktanya, beri tahu Pontiac, jika mereka tidak menyukainya,
mereka bisa mencium kacang kecilku.
Kamu sudah selesai atau kamu masih membutuhkanku?
Saya memiliki ide yang lebih baik daripada siapa pun!
Proposal itu adalah ide saya!
Lihat, Debbie,
jika Anda tidak menyukai pekerjaan Anda, saya bisa membelikan Anda yang baru.
Pengajuan tugas rekaman.
Tunggu, tidak, tidak, bukan itu--
Tugas pengiriman rekaman!
Woo! CINTA: Terisi Penuh!
Tolong jangan hari ini.
Kumohon.
Ini adalah set tertutup, saya ingin memberi tahu kalian.
Sejujurnya, saya tidak suka foto itu. Aku akan menandatanganinya.
Saya harus pergi dalam waktu sekitar dua detik.
- Tapi ini seperti gambar terbaik! - Baiklah.
Ya Tuhan.
Butuh tumpangan?
Oh, ayolah, bergembiralah.
Inilah yang terjadi saat Anda masih mengemudi
PT Cruiser ayahmu, dari SMA.
Kau akan membutuhkan mobil baru, sayang.
Aku baik-baik saja. Saya suka mobil saya.
Bukankah gila aku memulai sebagai magang Anda,
dan sekarang seperti, kita... seperti, saya seperti...
seperti sedikit di atas... seperti itu gila.
Yang gila adalah Kelley mengizinkan Anda membawa pulang mobil pertunjukan
tapi aku bahkan tidak bisa membuatnya melihatku.
Itu karena Kelley terobsesi padaku.
Ini akan menjadi seperti kotor
jika itu tidak datang dengan beberapa keuntungan.
Saya hanya memikirkan semua hal
Saya bermimpi tentang di sekolah menengah,
dan sekarang aku di sini, dan itu seperti,
apakah ini dia, apakah ini mimpinya?
Sungguh menjijikkan seberapa sering Anda berbicara tentang sekolah menengah.
Tidak, tapi serius, langgar saja aturannya.
Ada dua tipe orang kan?
Hiu dan ikan kecil.
Saya jelas hiu,
dan kau-kau ikan kecil.
Aku bukan ikan kecil.
Oke, kalau begitu buktikan.
Jika Anda ingin perhatian Kelley, lakukan saja apa yang saya lakukan.
Apa yang kamu lakukan?
Saya memintanya untuk telanjang dan kemudian saya memerasnya.
Aku bercanda!
Kau gila!
Um, tidak, aku melamar pekerjaan itu.
Jika itu membuatmu merasa lebih baik,
Saya benar-benar berpikir promosi itu milik Anda.
Anda layak mendapatkannya lebih dari siapa pun,
termasuk aku.
Saya menghasilkan terlalu banyak uang.
Anda ingin pergi ke sushi?
Bawa aku ke SUGARFISH.
Membawamu ke SUGARFISH.
Archer!
Tidak apa-apa.
Ini mendorong dirinya sendiri, kita bisa santai saja.
Duduk, santai.
Pintu ditutup.
- Hei! - Hai!
- Apakah kamu mendapatkannya? - Promosinya? Tidak.
Seksisme masih hidup dan sehat di Hollywood, sayang!
Apa?!
Orang-orang bodoh itu.
Tapi tidak, paketnya, maksud saya paketnya,
Oh, uh, ya.
- Lima menit, Nn. Pensky. - Terima kasih.
Kau di London? Saya pikir keynote Anda tidak sampai minggu depan.
Kami sedang merekamnya untuk peluncuran produk.
Buka. Saya hanya punya beberapa menit.
TekMate baru?! Ini bahkan belum keluar!
Saya kira membayar untuk mengenal penemunya!
Apakah kamu tidak ingin menyalakannya?
Wow, telepon tembus pandang yang tidak bisa dipecahkan.
Ini bahkan lebih baik secara langsung!
Ya Tuhan.
Apakah saya memberi tahu Anda bahwa saya dilamar malam itu
pada kencan kedua?
Ini seperti detik kita menginjak usia 30 tahun,
semua orang menjadi terobsesi...
"Maukah kamu menjadi pelayanku..."
Tunggu, apa itu...
Tidak.
Diam!
Quinn dan Logan akan menikah!
Maaf.
Dia bertemu saya di London dan mengejutkan saya dengan sebuah perjalanan
ke Belanda. Dia bahkan menyewa pesawat,
yang sangat tidak bertanggung jawab terhadap lingkungan, tapi...
- Tentu saja dia melakukannya! - Tentu saja dia melakukannya!
Jadi, saya baru saja menelepon Michael,
dan dia terobsesi menjadi petugas.
Dan saya mematikan telepon dengan Chase, dan dia ketakutan!
Oh. Hai-hai, Zoey!
Jadi kamu dengar.
- Dia akhirnya menjawab ya! - Hei, Logan!
Dan hanya butuh waktu 50 kali. Selamat!
Oke, jadi saya tahu ini hampir seperti terlalu cepat,
tapi pernikahannya harus tanggal 26 Agustus.
Singkat cerita, peluncuran produk,
ini satu-satunya saat saya bebas selama dua tahun ke depan.
Dan saya tidak tahu apa yang akan saya lakukan tanpa sahabat saya di sana.
Jadi bagaimana menurutmu?
Anda tahu, saya pikir saya harus bekerja,
tapi sepertinya aku benar-benar bebas!
Terima kasih. Hei, kau mau ambilkan aku air sebelum aku pergi?
Apapun untuk tunanganku.
Zo, kamu tahu itu akan baik-baik saja, kan?
Chase akan ada di sana. Ini akan baik-baik saja.
Lebih dari baik-baik saja, itu akan menyenangkan.
Tidak ada yang bisa melihatmu lagi kecuali aku.
Ini akan menjadi reuni yang kita semua butuhkan.
Aku harus pergi, sayang.
Silakan sambut penemu
Quinn Pensky.
Aku butuh minuman lagi.
* Anda dulu mengenal saya... *
"Tidak ada yang melihatmu lagi."
Aku melihat orang-orang.
Hanya karena aku sudah lama tidak melihatnya
bukan berarti kita bukan teman, kan?
Saya punya banyak teman, bertemu banyak orang.
Bahkan jika saya memiliki pilihan, saya terlalu sibuk.
Saya sangat sibuk sepanjang waktu.
* Dulu aku malaikatmu, sekarang aku berjalan keluar pintumu *
* Kamu bilang aku berubah menjadi jahat *
* Saya akan mengatakan bahwa saya akhirnya murni *
* Bersinar terang di bayanganku *
* Pikir saya kehilangan diri saya sebelumnya *
* Menahan saya, mengikat saya di dalam sangkar *
* Harus mengubah hidup saya *
* Karena aku tahu kamu akan tetap sama *
* Tidak dapat melihat Anda menghalangi jalan saya *
* Saya dapat melihat dengan jelas sekarang, sekarang, sekarang *
* Dulu kamu mengenalku, sekarang kamu tidak mengenalku *
* Anda dulu menghipnotis saya, melakukannya dengan sangat mudah *
Tentu saja saya punya pertanyaan.
Siapa yang menyelinap ke sekolah Minggu?
Siapa yang mencuri Subaru?
Dan siapa yang menikam Sarabella Simson?
Saya Stacey Dillsen, dan ini adalah Pembantaian Favorit saya.
* Aku seperti bunga yang mekar sejak aku meninggalkanmu *
* Tidak tahu apa yang saya lakukan *
- Woo! - Buat permintaan!
* Tahu kamu berubah menjadi jahat, kamu bilang aku kehilangan akal sehatku *
* Tidak, kamu tidak akan melakukan hal seperti itu padaku *
* Menahan saya, mengikat saya di dalam sangkar *
* Harus mengubah hidup saya *
* Karena aku tahu kamu akan tetap sama... *
Apakah ada kerang di dalamnya?
Tidak ada kerang!
* Sekarang kamu tidak *
* Anda dulu menghipnotis saya, melakukannya dengan sangat mudah *
* Dulu kamu mengenalku, sekarang kamu tidak mengenalku *
* Jangan menelusuri rol kamera Anda *
* Begitu banyak yang tidak Anda ketahui *
* Bahwa kamu lupa *
* Perjalanan yang luar biasa *
* Cara Anda dapat membalik *
* Melalui semua bagian yang baik darinya *
* Saya seharusnya tidak melakukannya *
* Urutan kronologis *
* Dan tidak lain hanyalah penyiksaan *
* Gulir terlalu jauh ke belakang... *
* Saya tidak ingin melihatnya *
* Tapi saya tidak bisa menghapusnya... *
Apa yang terjadi? Ya, berikan padaku.
Psh! Kerja bagus. Ya? Oke, ini dia.
Oh, ya. Kau hebat dalam hal itu.
Oh, ya, Anda ingin fistbump? Ayo pergi. Baiklah.
* Semua yang terbaik *
Chase, aku benar-benar minta maaf tentang Hawaii.
Tapi kami masih anak-anak. Bisakah kita bicara?
Oh, tidak, tidak, tidak, tidak.
Oh, tidak. Oh...
Anda sedang menonton LOVE: Fully Charged.
Jangan mengintip. Jangan mengintip. Jangan mengintip.
Oke, tunggu. Bertahanlah.
Kau siap? Tiga, dua, satu.
Ta-da!
Jordan B., ada apa? Apakah kamu melakukan semua ini?
Tidak.
Maksudku, ya.
Jordyn J., Aku tahu ini kencan kedua kita,
tapi ada sesuatu yang ingin kutanyakan padamu.
Oh, Tuhan.
Ya Tuhan!
Ya?
Um...
Apa yang salah dengan dia?
Greg, ada apa dengannya?
Entahlah. Dia tidak pernah seperti ini.
Yo, maafkan aku, tapi sebelum aku melakukan ini, bisakah aku bicara dengan Zoey?
Siapa Zoey?
Ah!
Zoey, kau mempermalukanku.
Jaringan menyukai gagasan Greg tentang proposal tersebut,
dan kemudian Jordan B. berlutut dan seperti,
"Eh, aku butuh Zoey. Dimana Zoey? Zoey, dimana Zoey?"
Nah, di mana saja kamu, Zoey?
Anda menempatkan saya pada tugas pengiriman rekaman.
Anda tidak di sini untuk menjawab.
Anda di sini untuk mendengarkan.
Saya tidak suka Jordan B.
Dia bertingkah seperti bayi.
Tapi Amerika tidak setuju.
Ini mungkin rambutnya.
Dan jika prediksi saya benar,
dia akan pergi ke final.
Dan ketika dia melakukannya, aku membutuhkanmu...
menjadi...
ibunya.
Ibu?
Ya.
Saat dia "lapar", Anda akan memberinya makan.
Saat dia pemarah, Anda akan memeriksa diapey-nya.
Dan saat kita ditayangkan,
Anda akan berada di telinganya untuk memberitahunya apa yang harus dikatakan,
karena aku tidak akan malu lagi.
Apakah ini berarti saya ada di tim langsung?
- Ya, baiklah, di tim siaran langsung. - Ya!
Oh, Tuhan.
Tidak, uh, tunggu, aku tidak bisa memberitahumu berapa lama aku menunggu untuk melakukan ini,
tapi saya tidak tahu apakah saya bisa menerimanya
karena ini akhir pekan yang sama dengan pernikahan sahabatku--
Aku tidak bertanya, oke?
Apapun rencanamu, batalkan, oke?
Kau sibuk.
- Terima kasih. - Terima kasih banyak.
Satu lagi.
Satu untuk satu. Hanya sedikit.
Quinn, ini aku, pelayan kehormatanmu.
Aku tidak bisa datang ke pernikahanmu.
Saya tahu ini adalah hari terpenting dalam hidup Anda,
tapi saya harus bekerja.
Oh, aku benci ini.
Zoey!
- Hai! Oh! - Hai!
Ya Tuhan, aku sangat senang kau ada di sini.
Keluargaku sudah membuatku gila.
Bubbe bilang aku terlalu pucat.
Ibuku pikir aku harus menambahkan ikat pinggang ke gaunnya.
Dan lirik adik Logan adalah -- / Quinn.
- Lirik. Hai. - Aku perlu bicara denganmu
- tentang hadiah pernikahanmu. - Sekarang?
Ya.
Hadiah saya adalah lagu asli.
Itu sangat bijaksana.
Bahwa saya akan tampil
saat Anda berjalan menyusuri lorong.
Lyric adalah penyanyi / penulis lagu yang sedang naik daun.
Saya mengkhususkan diri pada EDM / deep house / country-folk.
- Ini seperti semuanya. - Lirik, tentang hadiahnya--
Shh.
Ooh, itu sangat bagus.
Eh, maaf, melodinya baru saja datang padaku.
Aku harus meletakkan ini. Siri, buka memo suara.
Apa yang akan saya berikan untuk kepercayaan diri
dari anak dana perwalian.
Um, Quinn,
ada sesuatu yang benar-benar perlu saya bicarakan dengan Anda.
Siap, Nona Pensky?
Oh.
Maaf, aku -- aku harus pergi.
- Bicara nanti? Oke. - Ya, oke.
Terima kasih.
Kuharap dia muncul.
Zoey? Pelayan kehormatan? Mengapa dia tidak mau?
Karena dia tidak pernah muncul.
Dan bukannya kita tidak mengundangnya.
Sekarang setelah Anda menyebutkannya, saya bekerja dengan Quinn selama lima tahun
- dan aku masih belum bertemu dengannya. - Teori saya adalah
Saya pikir dia masih terjebak pada mantannya, Chase.
- Pria terbaik? - Dari SMA.
Ini menyedihkan. Mereka seharusnya menghabiskan musim panas
setelah tahun senior bersama di Hawaii,
tapi pasti ada sesuatu yang terjadi,
karena mereka putus, dan saya rasa tidak
dia memiliki hubungan sejak saat itu.
Oh, tidak. Hal yang buruk.
Dan jika dia muncul, itu akan menjadi tidak nyaman,
karena kurasa dia tidak tahu Chase punya pacar.
Yang serius. Kami makan malam bersama mereka di Baltimore
ketika saya sedang tur untuk pod saya.
Dia juga seorang guru.
Mereka sangat imut bersama.
- Astaga. - Zoey?
- Apakah kamu baik-baik saja? - Aku baik-baik saja. Aku sangat baik.
Pelayan kehormatanmu telah tiba!
- Hei! - Hai!
Sepertinya Anda bisa menggunakan sedikit minuman.
Terima kasih.
Nona Pensky, kamu terlihat cantik!
Senang bertemu denganmu, Zoey.
Oh, ini ibuku, nenek Quinn.
Bukan nenek. Tidak pernah nenek.
Bubbe.
Senang bertemu denganmu.
Bagaimana kabar keluargamu?
Apa yang sedang dilakukan adik kecilmu itu?
Tidak sedikit lagi.
Dia memiliki dua anak dan saudara kembar dalam perjalanan, jika Anda percaya.
Anda semua harus berhenti tumbuh dewasa.
- Mm-hmm. - Zoey!
- Sudah lama sekali! - Hai, Stacey!
Dan kau pasti Camille.
Ya, senang akhirnya bertemu denganmu.
Kami hanya ingin tahu apakah kau akan berhasil atau tidak.
Aku tahu. Aku terlambat, tapi aku ada di rumah pacarku.
Lupa waktu.
Pacar? Sejak kapan?
Ini baru-baru ini, tapi cukup tentang saya.
Sekarang, jangan membuat kita menunggu sampai pernikahan, Zoey.
Ayo, beri kami deets.
Ya, ya. Siapa namanya?
Eh, miliknya... namanya, um...
um...
Hemsworth.
Hugo Hemsworth.
Hemsworth? Apa dia orang Australia?
Ya.
Seperti Liam dan Chris Hemsworth?
Mereka adalah sepupu jauh.
- Oh! Apa yang dia lakukan? - Apa?
Dia seorang dokter.
Ahli bedah, sebenarnya.
- Wow! - Dr. Hemsworth.
Dia sudah siap.
Oh, syukurlah.
Dia tampak hebat.
Kamu terlihat luar biasa.
Bagaimana perasaanmu?
Seperti aku lebih suka menikah dengan jas lab.
Ini sempurna. Kau sempurna.
Kau sedikit pucat.
Bisa menggunakan ikat pinggang.
- Sampai ketemu lagi. - Baiklah. Dah!
- Uh, hei, di mana mobilmu? - Oh, ada di toko.
- Oh. Apa kau butuh tumpangan? - Itu sangat manis,
tapi pacarku menjemputku.
- Apa-apa? - Sebenarnya, mobilnya.
Itu mengemudi sendiri.
Mengemudi sendiri?
- Fancy! - Ya.
Uh, permisi? Pacar? Apa yang saya lewatkan?
Inikah yang ingin kamu bicarakan?
Ya Tuhan, apakah kamu membawanya ke pesta pernikahan?
- Ini sangat besar! - Tidak, tidak, tidak.
Sudah terlambat untuk menambahkan nilai tambah.
Tidak, tidak. Saya benar-benar mengirim SMS ke perencana pernikahan kami.
Yang mengingatkan saya, maukah Anda pergi ke Santa Barbara?
Logan mengubah ukuran cincinnya di tempat yang mewah,
dan tidak ada orang yang lebih aku percayai selain kamu.
Apa kau keberatan?
- Aku tidak keberatan. Aku akan melakukannya. - Terima kasih.
Oh! Aku mencintaimu.
- Mwah. - Aku menyayangimu. Dah!
Dan saat itulah saya tahu saya harus melakukan keduanya:
pernikahan dan final.
* Dulu bayi, dulu wanita *
* Pikir Anda adalah kekasih yang sempurna... *
Jika saya akan melakukan ini,
Saya membutuhkan tiga hal:
Pacar, mobil, dan rencana.
Pernikahan berlangsung pada pukul 4: 00.
di perkebunan keluarga Logan di Malibu.
Final langsung berlangsung pada pukul 5: 00.
pada CINTA: Tahap terisi penuh,
hanya 2,3 mil di jalan.
Pada saat saya dibutuhkan di lokasi syuting,
resepsi pernikahan akan berjalan lancar.
Saya akan menyelinap pergi untuk mengerjakan final,
dan kembalilah sebelum ada yang menyadari aku pergi.
Ini sangat mudah.
Selanjutnya, saya membutuhkan mobil.
Mobil yang bisa mengemudi sendiri.
Mengamankan kunci itu mudah.
Kelley membiarkan Archer mengambil LUV-6 kapan pun dia mau,
dan dia dengan senang hati menyerahkannya.
Tunggu, kau naik mobil?
Zoey, kembali ke sini!
Apa? Ugh!
* Waktu untuk berjalan *
Ugh, terima kasih Tuhan.
Siswa telah menjadi master.
Sekarang, yang saya butuhkan hanyalah kencan.
Tapi di mana saya seharusnya menemukan seorang jagoan
Ahli bedah UGD Australia yang bernama Hugo Hemsworth?
Yo, ada apa? Namaku Dragon.
Nama asli saya adalah Vantarius,
tapi saya penggemar Game of Thrones yang sangat besar,
jadi saya secara resmi mengubah nama saya ketika saya berusia 18 tahun.
Ayolah, siapa yang bisa menolak ini?
Namaku Spencer, dan aku tahu apa yang diinginkan wanita.
Dia mungkin tidak ada.
Yang saya butuhkan adalah seorang aktor.
Halo, nama saya Todd E. Schupert.
Umurku 28 tahun.
Saya seorang aktor dari Burbank, California.
Saya juga bisa melakukan aksen. Saya bisa melakukan Australia.
Saya baru saja keluar dari Bondi Beach.
G'day, apa kabar?
Dan di situlah Anda masuk.
Melihat r Anda sum,
Saya dapat melihat bahwa Anda memiliki pelatihan bertahun-tahun,
lusinan film mahasiswa di bawah ikat pinggang Anda.
BFA dalam Akting.
Oh, dan anak di bawah umur dalam Perkembangan Anak Usia Dini.
- Keren. - Tidak, tidak, tidak.
Saya manny untuk keluarga di samping.
Oke, saya bisa berhenti jika Anda membutuhkannya.
Tidak ada acara TV atau film besar. Itu bagus.
Oke, jadi, maaf, apa hubungannya ini dengan
dengan saya mendapatkan CINTA: Terisi Penuh ?
Todd, aku di sini bukan untuk bicara denganmu
tentang jatuh CINTA: Terisi Penuh.
Saya melihat rekaman kiriman Anda,
dan aku menggunakan kekuatanku untuk membawamu ke sini.
Itu salah, dan saya minta maaf tentang itu.
Oke, jadi mengapa aku di sini?
Aku butuh bantuan.
Saya membutuhkan seseorang untuk memerankan pacar saya
di pernikahan sahabatku akhir pekan depan.
Saya membutuhkan mereka untuk berkomitmen penuh
cara yang hanya bisa dilakukan oleh aktor sungguhan.
Oke. Jadi, seperti, metode.
Tentu. Ya.
I...
Saya tidak tahu mengapa saya pikir ini ide yang bagus.
Lupakan tanyaku. Maafkan aku.
Tidak, tidak, tidak. Oke, jika saya melakukan ini,
bisakah Anda mengajak saya ke acara itu?
Maksud saya, saya pasti bisa mencoba.
Itu cukup bagus untukku.
* Anda dan saya sudah selesai, meskipun *
* Saksikan aku memukulnya sendirian *
* Saya akan melakukannya secara akapela, ya *
Apakah ini benar-benar gila?
Bagian mana, mempekerjakan aktor super seksi untuk memerankan pacar Anda
di pernikahan sahabat Anda, atau setuju untuk bekerja
akhir pekan yang sama dengan pernikahan sahabatmu?
Bagian pacar.
Meyakinkan teman-teman Anda bahwa Anda memiliki pacar yang seksi
adalah kekhawatiran Anda yang paling kecil jika dia tidak memperhatikan jalan.
Apakah dia tahu apa yang dia lakukan?
Mobil itu mengemudi sendiri,
dan kinerjanya sangat baik selama fase pengujian keamanan.
Itu menabrak enam boneka tabrakan.
Um, halo? Arch?
Aku kehilanganmu mengemudi melewati ngarai.
Pelayanan yang buruk.
Mobil akan kembali sebelum pertunjukan ditayangkan.
Oke, dah!
Ini tombol merahnya, Zoey.
Tombol merah besar. Pusat. Ya, di sana. Akhir--
Uh, apa yang kau baca?
Oh, ada lima langkah untuk menciptakan karakter yang sempurna.
Siapa, apa, kapan, di mana, dan mengapa.
Saya punya empat yang pertama, kan? Jadi siapa:
Hugo Boss Hemsworth.
Apa: dia adalah ahli bedah ER yang terkenal
siapa yang jatuh cinta dengan Zoey Brooks.
Kapan: hari ini.
Dimana: lahir di Melbourne.
Dibesarkan di West Philly.
Anda benar-benar mengambil beberapa kebebasan di sana.
Saya tidak bisa menjelaskan alasannya.
Anda tahu, interpretasi saya adalah bahwa dia sedang dimanfaatkan
sebagai alat untuk membuat mantan pacar Anda cemburu.
- Apakah itu benar? - Cemburu?
Tidak, tidak, tidak, sama sekali tidak.
Itu akan menjadi tidak dewasa.
Saya hanya ingin menunjukkan padanya dan semua orang
bahwa saya adalah orang dewasa yang sangat sukses dan berpengetahuan luas
siapa yang pindah dan melakukan yang lebih baik darinya.
Dimengerti.
J-E-A-lous.
Hai. Oh, terima kasih banyak sudah datang. Dasi yang bagus.
- Terima kasih. - Sampai ketemu di luar sana.
Saya tidak tahu harus berkata apa, Chauncy,
dia hanya tidak cukup cepat.
Bawakan aku bajingan lagi. Tidak, tidak, tidak, bawakan aku dua.
Orang-orang membutuhkan tiram.
Aku melihat pengantin wanitanya.
Hai. Itu dia.
- Aku sudah mencarimu. - Maafkan aku, sayang.
Saya telah memadamkan api ke kiri dan ke kanan.
Bukankah itu gunanya perencana pernikahan?
- Ya, aku memecatnya. - Kamu apa?
Dengar, dia hanya-- Dia tidak menjalankan visinya.
Saya pikir akhir pekan ini seharusnya
santai dan akrab.
250 orang itu akrab, sayang.
Tahukah Anda berapa banyak orang yang tidak saya undang?
- Ini hanya sedikit berlebihan. - Sedikit banyak?
Kami mendapat dua kue seukuran aslinya
dari kedua mempelai untuk diantar.
Ya. Di sana baik-baik saja.
- Wow. - Lihat, Quinn,
ini akhir pekan pernikahan kita, oke?
Kamu bekerja sangat keras,
anda pantas mendapatkan lebih dari sedikit.
Anda pantas mendapatkan yang paling banyak.
Aku hanya ingin memberikannya padamu.
Aku tahu kau tahu.
- Quinn! Logan! - Michael.
Kamu terlihat luar biasa!
- Tidak, tidak, tidak! - Ini kue!
Oh, tunggu, apa? Ini kue?
- Ya. - Sial!
Bisakah seseorang mengeluarkan kue manusia ini dari sini,
sebelum aku meleleh?
- Oh! - Senang bertemu denganmu.
- Aku sangat senang kau ada di sini. - Buddy.
Oh, bung, saya sangat senang bahwa ini akhirnya terjadi.
Dua sahabat saya akan menikah?
Mengambil risiko, dan saya bisa menjerumuskannya?
Ini benar-benar suatu kehormatan. Jujur.
Oh, berbicara tentang upacara,
Saya ingin membahas apa yang saya miliki sejauh ini.
Saya mendapat, seperti, lima draf.
Aku sudah menulis, oke?
"Yang terkasih..."
Ini dia, Todd.
Keberatan memanggilku Hugo?
Itu hanya membantu saya tetap berkarakter.
Sekarang tolong, biarkan saya mengambil waktu saya sebelumnya.
Todd.
"Kami berkumpul di sini untuk melewati hal yang disebut kehidupan ini."
Ada apa dengan mobil itu?
- Todd. - Saya tidak kenal siapa pun bernama Todd.
- Mobil itu. Mobilnya! - Oh, Tuhan.
Awas!
Oh!
- Oh, Tuhan! - Pintu terbuka.
- Saya pikir itu... - Kau baik-baik saja? Semuanya baik-baik saja?
Ada apa?
You almost hit us
with your car!
It's called making an entrance,
Logan.
All right. I'll accept that.
That's a pretty good entrance.
I mean, damn!
-What's up, Zoey?
-Michael, it's been too long.
Yeah, no shit, we live in the
same city and we barely see you.
-What's up with that?
-'Cause she's too busy
putting up with my ass.
Apologies for my appearance.
I had to come
straight from surgery.
-Surgery?
-This is Hugo.
-Hugo, this is...
-Quinn and Logan!
The bride and the groom.
Of course I know
who you are.
Zoey's told me so much
about you.
- Love your car.
- Thank you.
And you must be Michael?
Yes. The officiant, Michael.
-Pardon?
-The officiant.
You know, you said their titles,
you know, bride and groom,
but I'm Michael,
the officiant.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-That's awesome.
-Yeah, it is awesome.
It's an honor, actually.
Yeah. Yeah.
Um, hon, I'm gonna go
put the bags in our room.
Quinn, could you point me
in the right direction?
The wedding party is staying
in the guest quarters upstairs.
Yeah, I'll show them up.
Come on, Michael.
Thanks.
Somebody clean up that glass.
Okay, where did you find him?
He's perfect.
Tell me about it.
So how are things going?
Oh, uh... well, you'll see.
Welcome. Welcome, everyone.
Cheers to Logan and Quinn.
Cheers!
I got that second shucker
on site.
All right, I'm taking him
to you now.
I said two trays.
So then I'm thinking
of closing with a joke.
You know, since everyone
will be sobbing at that point.
You gotta wake up.
I'm trying to rehearse here.
What a disgusting
display of wealth.
God, I hate rich people.
Uh, don't you live here?
It's journalism.
The case I'm working on now
is a real stumper.
They call him
the Malibu Murderer.
He's still at large.
-So you're a detective?
-Podcast host.
Logan! Quinn!
Oh, look, I'm so glad
you wore makeup
Bubbe, that's a cake.
-That's a cake?
-Yeah. Come on. Come on.
Don't talk to that.
I see. This is big,
even for Logan.
Yeah, I don't even know
half these people here.
Well, you know me,
and I'm here for anything at all
that you need,
whether it's a refill
or a rescue.
Hey, babe?
I really need you right now.
Aunt Carol and her bridge club
want a photo.
-Okay, I'll rescue you.
-Like, now.
Save you in a bit.
Sleeping arrangements
aren't gonna be a problem.
The rooms are huge.
I situated myself on the couch
like a gentleman.
And didn't think to change.
Zoey, I'm creating a character,
okay?
-Mm-hmm.
-I just...
I need you to trust the work.
Now, which one is the ex?
I don't think he's here yet.
Okay, good, I'm gonna go
get us some drinks.
Oh!
Chase.
Here.
Uh...
Hi.
Hi!
Oh, um...
this is my girlfriend,
Danielle.
-Hi.
-So excited to be here.
It's like a dream,
meeting everyone
Chase keeps talking about
from high school.
Nice to meet you. I'm--
Ah. Let me guess.
Dana.
Lola?
-Coco?
-Zoey. I'm Zoey.
Chase, I don't remember you
mentioning a Zoey.
Yeah, well, must have
slipped my mind.
Ah, sorry.
Vodka martini,
slightly dirty.
Mm, just like you, cowgirl.
Hi, I'm Hugo Hemsworth,
Zoey's boyf.
Oh! Boyf.
Wow, that's a strong grip.
-And jawline.
-Thank you.
I... am Chase.
Chase.
Danielle.
-Hi, nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hang on one second.
-Yes, babe, sure.
Um, I have to take this.
-So nice to meet you, Danielle.
-Likewise.
Chase, I had something
I wanted to tell you,
but must have slipped my mind.
See you.
See you, sexy.
You'll have to excuse
the scrubs.
I had to come straight
from surgery.
-Surgery?
-Wow.
We pulled a double.
Heart and brain
at the same time.
That's amazing.
* Well, good for you *
* I guess you moved on
really easily *
* Found a new girl, and it only
took a couple weeks *
* Remember when you said you
wanted to give me the world? *
* World *
* And good for you *
* I guess that you've been
working on yourself *
* I guess that therapist
I found for you *
* She really helped *
* Now you can be a better man *
* For your brand-new girl *
Sorry, I was getting
the car detailed.
-Please!
-Oh, the shoes.
Then take them off.
Take them off.
-Greg.
-Okay, here.
Leave her shoes--
Leave them there!
Okay.
Oh, sorry. Okay, okay.
Perhaps you'd care
to explain...
this.
The thing I love most
about Jordyn J.
is probably her boobs.
Oh, my God. The hair...
looks so...
good.
So you knew about this
and you let it happen?
Because the hair?
That was it.
That was all that he had.
That's exactly why.
He wanted to show Jordyn J.
and America
that he's more
than just his hair.
Uh, he's a trendsetter.
It's called strategy.
Is it?
Kelley, being your first
and only female producer,
you just got to trust me
on this.
I know what our audience wants
because I am our audience.
And I love the hair.
For your own sake,
I hope that you are right.
Okay.
Zoey?
Seriously.
Hot dress.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Now I take you seriously.
Okay. Thanks.
Greg!
Punch you in the face.
Just pumping away,
trying to get a pulse.
Seven-year-old kid
swallowed a ping-pong ball.
-So sad.
-Oh, my God.
No, no, no. Don't worry.
He is fine.
Nobody has ever died
on my table.
Aw!
Except maybe a couple times.
Who even is this guy?
Shh. He's so sweet.
You know what?
Enough about me.
Stacey, I'm a huge fan
of the pod.
Total Slaughter-head.
- Oh!
- Yeah.
Any updates
on the Malibu Murderer?
Oh. Um... you listen?
Ahem. I'm back.
This is Mark, my field producer.
-Husband.
-Uh-huh.
But, yes, also field producer.
Didn't you and Quinn
used to...?
Date. Yes.
Yeah, it was just a fling.
But this, uh...
-This is the real deal.
-Excuse me.
How was it with the witness?
-I got a description...
-Yes, Mark. Great work.
...of his hands.
Damn it, Mark,
that's not enough.
But go on.
She said the hands
were large.
That's it?
Not guilty!
- They're enormous.
- Oh, so funny!
Jordan B.,
why is your hair orange?
I thought I could fix it
without anyone noticing.
Fix what?
I found a gray hair, okay?
You happy?
I can't have gray hair at 23.
I'm supposed to be hot.
You bleached your whole head
because of one gray hair?
Then it kind of started
falling out, so I had to cut it.
I tried to find you first,
but you weren't here.
I'm sorry. I know.
It's just...
Hang on. One second.
Um...
-I'm gonna have to leave again.
-What?
If you need anything at all,
you call me.
Not Kelley, okay? Me.
You're gonna be fine.
What was I saying?
Oh, yeah. Jordyn's boobs.
Om...
* Cha cha *
* Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da *
* If you wanna have some fun *
* Come with me
I'll give you some *
* Get back, get back *
So, in a way,
I credit Zoey
for saving
that little boy's life.
- Aw!
- Yeah, she...
- So sweet.
- Oh, my God.
She inspires me
to be a better surgeon.
- Aw!
- Wow.
Can you take a look at my feet?
Because--
-Whoa!
-What is that?!
I'm sorry, it stinks.
Don't smell it. Just fix it.
Quinn?
- Jordan B., what do you want?
- Zoey.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
It's gonna--
It's gonna be okay.
No! A neck tattoo will not fix
what you did to your hair.
Who's getting a neck tattoo?
I-I have to go.
Quinn, I've been looking
all over for you.
What are you doing
in the bathtub?
I'm unclogging the drain.
Did you know clogged drains can
lead to corrosion and flooding?
Oh no.
Okay, what's wrong?
I never dreamed
of having a wedding.
But then I fell in love
with someone who did.
And I want to do this for him,
but it's all a lot.
Does Logan know that?
We've been together
over a decade. You'd think so.
But he's so totally absorbed,
it's like
he's a different person.
I know he's dreamed of having
an extravagant wedding,
and I'm trying
to be sensitive to that.
But I'm not a rational function.
My limits are not infinite.
If only humans
could have vertical asymptotes,
you know what I'm saying?
Not at all.
But I think I get
the gist of it.
So why don't we just
get out of here.
Leave my own party?
I don't think I'm allowed
to do that.
You're the bride.
You can do whatever you want.
Party's almost over.
Plus, there's a cake down there
that everyone thinks
is you anyway.
-Where would we even go?
-I have ideas.
Seriously?
A karaoke bar?
No, no, no, no. It's late.
The rehearsal's tomorrow.
- We gotta be rested.
- Hey!
Look at me.
I love you.
I love you too.
So stop thinking about
the wedding for one second
and have some fun with me,
okay?
Fine.
- Okay. All right.
- Yeah!
But if Michael doesn't sing
Limp Bizkit, I'm leaving.
Cool. Everyone's drinks
are on Logan. Let's go inside.
Let's go. Come on, babe.
- That's it, Logan.
- Let's do this.
-You good?
-I'm good. You good?
-Yeah. Great.
-Good.
* Chocolate stardust *
* Keep on rolling, baby *
* Throw your hands up *
* Now move in, now move out,
hands up, now hands down *
* Back up, back up,
tell me what you gonna do now *
* Breathe in, now breathe out,
hands up, now hands down *
* Back up, back up,
tell me what you gonna do now *
* Keep rollin', rollin',
rollin', rollin' *
* Keep rollin',
rollin', rollin', rollin' *
* Keep rollin', rollin',
rollin', rollin' *
* Keep rollin'... *
Yeah! This is my favorite!
Rollin', rollin'!
* I know y'all be lovin
this ish right here *
* L-I-M-P Bizkit
is right here *
* Gonna F you up,
shut the F up *
* And back the F up
while we F this track up *
* You wanna mess
with Limp Bizkit? *
* You can't mess
with Limp Bizkit *
* 'Cause we get it on
every day and every night *
Was he always that talented?
Yeah, but in school
it was mostly sad flute music.
Oh, yes!
So you all went
to high school together?
Yeah! PCA, baby!
So sad what happened.
We were the last class
to attend Pacific Coast Academy.
The school closed down in 2009
when multiple parents complained
about poor education standards,
leading the state to launch
a formal investigation,
only to discover the school
wasn't even accredited
and Dean Rivers was stealing
students' tuition
and blowing it
at Morongo Casino and Resort.
Yeah, it wasn't even
a real school.
The student loans were real! Ha!
I have so much debt!
* Keep rollin', rollin',
rollin', rollin' *
* Rollin' *
Woo!
-Let's go!
-Great job, buddy. Great job.
- Let's do it.
- That was awesome!
I'm gonna hit the head.
Does anybody need anything?
Chase? Maybe a water?
Yes.
All right, I'll be right back.
-Consent to a kiss?
-Granted.
All right, next up,
we have Hugo Hemsworth
and Chase Matthews
singing a duet.
No, I'm all set.
Babe, you love karaoke. Go!
Chase! Chase! Chase! Chase!
-Yes!
-Woo!
Yes, Chase!
Go, Chase, go!
Hope you're cool
with the high part.
Uh, what song are we even--
* Now I've had *
* The time of my life *
* No, I never felt
like this before *
Damn it, I love this song.
* Yes, I swear *
* It's the truth *
* And I owe it all to you *
* 'Cause I've had *
* The time of my life *
* And I owe it all to you *
-Yo, they're both...
-Pretty good!
-Yeah.
-Let's go, Chase!
Not bad.
Bet you didn't know
I was a high tenor, did you?
* I've been waiting
for so long *
* Now I finally
found someone *
* To stand by me *
* We saw the writing
on the wall *
* As we felt
this magical fantasy *
* Now with passion
in our eyes *
* There's no way
we could disguise it secretly *
* So we take
each others' hand *
* 'Cause we seem to understand
the urgency *
-Are they...?
-Wasted?
One of them is.
* I've had *
* The time of my life *
* No, I never felt
this way before *
* Yes, I swear *
* It's the truth *
* And I owe it all to you *
See that bod?
Yes!
Calm down.
I can't dance like that.
No, come on! Come on!
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Are you okay?
I am so sorry, dude.
What is this?
What? I thought we were
just having fun.
This is about Zoey, isn't it?
You're mad we dated so you're
trying to make me jealous.
Well, that's not gonna work,
Mr. Sexy Doctor Man,
because I don't care
about Zoey anymore.
-What's happening?
-Looks like they're fighting.
Let's just chill out.
That's it. I'm over it!
I'm over her!
-Well, doesn't sound like it.
-What'd you say?
I just get the feeling
that maybe you're not
actually over her.
You're getting a bit heavy.
Ah!
- What?
- Up! Up!
What is your problem?
Oh, boo-hoo! Time for rehearsal!
Out of bed!
Everybody outside in ten!
What is the matter with you?
Can't he leave me alone
for one minute?
I'm so sick
of babysitting this guy.
I cannot do this today.
-Todd.
-Hmm?
Aren't you a manny?
It's a side gig, but yeah.
-Hmm?
-No!
No. I'm your fake boyfriend.
Fake hungover boyfriend.
I'm not your babysitter.
Please. Please.
Meet me in the chapel in ten!
I have to go be with my friends.
I really need your help on this.
Please.
The villa is just
right up the street.
You can go up there,
distract him, have fun.
-Please, please, please?
-Wait, so I get to go to set?
Yes. Thank you.
Oh, my God. Finally.
Places! Okay.
So we're gonna start
with Michael
making an announcement
to ask all the guests
to silence their phones.
Cue Michael.
Silence your phone.
Bro, what is going on?
"I think I lost my voice."
How do you know
what he's saying?
I'm really good at lip-reading.
From over there?
- Plus, I have 20/20 vision.
- Great.
So my officiant
has lost his voice
the day before the wedding!
This is why we can't have fun.
"Let me show you. Ready?"
Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here today
to celebrate this thing
called patriarchy.
Heard of it?
Which has been used
for centuries to oppress women
by buying and selling them.
It's also kept the majority of
wealth in the male minority.
Okay, thank you, Lyric.
Look, I'm sorry, buddy,
but I gotta replace you.
- "Son of a--"
- Fine.
-I'll do it.
-What?
I have the number one
murder podcast in the U.S.
People would literally kill
to have me officiate
their wedding.
Yeah, you make a fair point.
But who's gonna
walk me down the aisle?
-It's a straight line, babe.
-Michael, obviously.
"Okay, sounds good."
Let's try this again.
Stacey will ask everyone
to silence their phones.
Get out of here, buddy.
Cue Stacey.
Silence your phones!
Just a little less creepy
next time, okay?
Yeah, okay.
Lyric's gonna sing us in.
Lyric!
My AI gloves weren't programmed
to deal with that reverb.
Did you hear the echo?
All right, guys, get in places.
Michael, Mark,
Camille and Jared, come on.
-Tighten up.
-How's your nose?
How do you think?
Your boyfriend dropped me
on my face on purpose.
He did not do it on purpose.
Zoey, he's very strong.
His muscles are huge.
He definitely
could have held me.
Classic Chase.
Taking everything so personally.
He said he was sorry.
All right,
cue Camille and Jared.
Chase, I know it's awkward,
but for the sake of our friends,
can't we at least just try
to be friends?
I'm sorry, but after
everything that happened,
did you really think
we were gonna be able
to just link arms
and stroll off into the sunset?
All right, now Zoey and Chase
will link arms and stroll.
Okay, the timing of that
was unfair.
They're linking.
They're strolling.
You could look happy.
Okay, cue the bride.
And, frankly, there is
no amount of philanthropy
that will ever make up
for those mistakes.
Lastly,
Quinn, you have come up
with so many wonderful
inventions over the years,
but I think
that your most impressive yet
is actually the reinvention
of this guy right here,
my best friend.
He's become an amazing man
because of you.
And so I think I speak
for all of us
when I say thank you very much,
Quinn.
To Quinn and Logan. Everyone.
To Quinn and Logan!
This is nice.
Stace, isn't this nice?
Everyone together,
celebrating?
Mm-hmm. Mark, tell me something.
You're my field producer, right?
And husband.
Then why aren't you
in the field?
I thought we'd take
the night off.
Can the women
who are being murdered
take the night off, Mark?
But...
couldn't he be here?
-What?
-I'm just saying,
technically couldn't
the Malibu Murderer
be at this wedding
in Malibu?
How dare you, Mark?
These are our closest
and dearest friends.
-You're so right.
-Why would there be a murderer
-at this wedding?
-Just forget I said it.
Enjoy your fish.
-Where's Hugo?
-Oh.
Um, uh...
he got called in
for an emergency.
If only there were more
people like him in the world.
Hey, Zoe, your turn.
Like yesterday.
Oh, right. Yeah, okay.
I would like to make a toast.
I've known Quinn and Logan
for more than half my life.
During that time,
I've watched Quinn grow,
evolve, and accomplish
almost all of her dreams.
And I've watched Logan
watch her do that.
Everyone says that high school
love doesn't last,
and they're right.
Most of the time, it doesn't.
Against all odds,
Quinn and Logan
have proved them wrong.
Uh... um...
uh, that's why it's so real
and inspiring.
Just really makes me,
you know, just dance a little
and, um...
...just really gets me
so excited, I just want
to sing and drink a lot.
Yeah!
To Quinn and Logan!
I'm such a klutz.
I'm gonna have to go change.
You missed your mouth
by a lot.
I know. I'm sorry.
I'll be right back, okay?
What is going on?
Why is he here?
And what is on his face?
I'm an ice tiger. Grr!
Todd, what happened?
You told me to babysit.
So I took him to the pier.
He wanted to ride
the kiddy coaster, right?
But he's too big, so he hit
his head on the support beam.
Now he can't remember
the last six months of his life.
Including the show,
or Jordyn J.
What?
My God.
Did I just hear a lion?
No. My dad made me get rid
of all my exotic pets.
It's not that big of a deal.
Right? It's okay.
I mean, wasn't Jordan B.
pretty stupid already?
You're right, maybe nobody
will even notice.
I mean, I'm gonna be telling him
exactly what to say.
Okay, I need to get back
down there.
So you're gonna sneak him
into the villa,
put him to sleep,
he'll sleep this off,
and everything will be--
Oh.
Door opening.
Door closing.
Zoey, it is show day.
You said you were gonna
have the car back in time,
so where's the car, babe?
Archer, I promise you,
the car is the least
of your worries.
Have you seen Jordan B. today?
Is he acting a little,
um, I don't know, different?
Oh, hey!
-Hi.
-Hey!
Whoa!
Just as dumb as usual. Why?
No reason! Look, I'm on my way
with the car.
I just have to make a little
pit stop in Santa Barbara.
Santa Barbara?
That is not on the way.
Okay, um...
What do I do?
No.
Door opening.
Oh, my God!
I'm so sorry! I did not mean to!
Oh, Chase.
It's you.
Zoey!
If my nose wasn't broken before,
I think it might be now.
Why are you even up this early?
I went on a run.
Why are you even up right now?
Is your nose bleeding?
Oh, here, I have some tissues.
Door closing.
-Uh, no...
-Wait, no, no, no!
Wait, wait!
Navigation calculated.
Estimated time:
one hour, 12 minutes.
Zoey? Turn it off.
I don't know how.
You don't know
how to work your own car?
-Come on.
-Turn off!
- Door. Stop car.
- Uh...
Cancel trip.
New drive time:
one hour, 59 minutes.
Why did it just go up?
-Quinn?
-Here comes the bride.
All dressed in really pretty
pink pajamas. Hello?
-Wedding day!
-Good morning!
-You all look so good!
-You do!
Where's Zoey?
-Oh.
-Zoey?
Zoey?
-Zoe?
-Zoey?
It's showtime, baby.
Can you at least tell me
where we're going?
Cool, I guess we'll just
sit in silence then.
Chase, you made it very clear
that you don't want to hear
what I have to say.
I thought that maybe
this weekend,
we could put our past
behind us and act like adults,
but clearly we cannot.
So, yes, I think it's best
if we don't speak.
Playing "Don't Speak."
* You and me *
* We used to be together *
* Every day, together *
* Always *
* I really feel *
* That I'm losing
my best friend *
* I can't believe
this could be the end *
* Don't speak *
* I know just what
you're saying *
* So please stop explaining *
* Don't tell me,
'cause it hurts *
Ladies, are we decent?
Hugo, what are you
doing here?
Zoey's dealing with a little
work emergency,
-so she sent me.
-Wow.
Who wants mimosas?
Yes!
-Everybody take a glass.
-Is everything okay?
Here you go.
Everything is fine.
-She's gonna be right back.
-Okay.
Arriving
at Perry's Fine Jewelry.
But Logan said
you got the rings already.
Doors opening.
Thank God.
Let's get out of here.
This thing's horrible.
It's like a prison on wheels.
Doors closing.
Self-park activating.
Oh. Heh.
Hey, is that the car
from LOVE: Fully Charged ?
No.
I'm pretty sure it is.
No, it's not.
These are really nice.
Even I would like for you
to buy me some of these.
You know, if you want
somebody on the side,
I am that person.
We are appointment only.
You have an appointment?
Um, we're here to pick up.
-Name?
-Reese. Logan and Quinn.
Oh, Mr. and Mrs. Reese.
Stop playing with me. You know
you got no money. Go home.
Oh! Mr. and Mrs. Reese,
I did not recognize your voice.
I spoke to y'all over the phone.
Remember me? Janice.
-No, that's actually not...
-No. We're not...
Honestly, it's fine.
My mama say I'm forgettable.
But you two are late.
I thought maybe
you was trying to ditch us
and get your rings
down the street.
Pauline! Kayla!
-The Reese family is here!
-Oh, my God.
The rings will be right out.
-Oh!
Pauline! Kayla!
Oh, this is a lot.
-Uh, no.
-Uh, no. We're fine.
- Take it.
Okay.
We love giving high-paying
customers like yourself
the full VIP treatment.
We hope you don't mind.
-We actually have to go.
-Yeah, we need to leave.
Oh, come on, you're never gonna
be as in love as you are now.
And it might not even last.
-Probably won't.
-That's a weird thing to say.
Okay. Oh!
A toast to the bride and groom.
Cheers!
So, Quinn and Logan,
what's your story?
-Again, we're actually not...
-We don't want to...
Oh, come on, don't be
those people, so boring.
Don't even think
about being those people.
You're not gonna get these rings
until you spill the tea.
Now, where did you meet?
Well, we met in middle school.
Oh, young love. I love.
Then what?
He saw me and ran his bike
into a flagpole.
-No. A flagpole?
-I'm dead.
-Then we became best friends.
-Study buddies.
But everybody knew
I had a thing for her.
And no one knew
I had a thing for him.
-They knew.
-They did not.
But every time I tried
to take it to the next level,
something always got in the way.
Other boyfriends.
-Other girlfriends.
-Yikes. We don't like that.
-Distance.
-Mm-hmm.
-Mistakes.
-Ugh.
But anyway, here we are
getting married now.
It's great,
so fast-forward to now.
We'd love our rings.
Kiss. Kiss. Kiss.
Kiss. Kiss. Kiss. Kiss. Kiss.
-Actually, we're just gonna...
-Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
-We're just gonna...
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Guys, seriously?
-We're actually gonna head.
-We should leave, right?
This is a lot.
And the champagne was...
* I'm just waiting
for your love *
* You know you are
the only one *
* That I think of *
* And all I want to do
is fuel the fire *
Oh.
-Seriously, these suck.
-Every single one.
Blurry.
No, actually,
Zoey's the big spoon
and I'm the little spoon.
We're cute like that.
Hugo, you are hilarious.
Where did you grow up again?
Burbank.
Uh... Brisbane.
Australia. Brisbane.
Sometimes I use an
Australian accent when I go out.
You wouldn't believe
how many men, women,
and nonbinary people I get
when I use this voice.
Hey, Hugo, could you text
Zoey for me?
I've tried a bunch of times,
but she hasn't responded.
Yeah, can do.
I'll get us a bottle
while I'm out.
All right, see you soon.
Ugh. Aussies are the best.
Hey, Logan, here's an idea.
I can still officiate
the wedding
using text to voice.
What? No, dude.
Absolutely not.
Look, I can't find Chase
anywhere. Where is he?
Dude, I can't hear
a single thing you're saying.
Where is he?
-I'll text him.
Thank you, Jared.
Jared, you suck.
Really, Michael?
Is that what happens
when you get engaged?
Free champagne
everywhere you go?
No, that's what happens
when you drop
six figures on a ring.
So, um, you think you and Hugo
will get engaged?
No.
I'm-I'm-- I mean, no.
Not really thinking
about marriage.
But what about you?
Danielle? No.
I mean, she's great.
Um, for now.
Uh, you know,
the timing just felt right.
Timing. Something we never had.
I'm so sorry about Hawaii.
I tried to call.
I sent messages.
And I completely understand
why you didn't respond,
but I wanted the chance
to explain why I--
Left me alone on a literal
island and waited weeks to call?
Yeah, why did you do that?
I guess I was so used to it
not working out between us
that I was scared
of what would happen
if it actually did.
So I just bailed.
I really, really wish I hadn't.
I mean, I've tried to move on.
I've tried to forget.
I threw myself into work.
Distanced myself
from all of our friends.
I even downloaded
every dating app on Earth.
But no matter what I did,
it always came back to you.
I know that sounds
so ridiculous, but it's why...
Why is the car stopping?
Zero percent charge.
Oh, my gosh.
You have to charge this car.
Yeah, that's kind of a thing.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
Is that what you're wearing?
Yeah, why?
No reason.
-Anything yet from Zoey?
-No.
Calls are going
straight to voicemail.
Why is...
...nothing going through?
Yeah, I think I had
better over here, actually.
What am I gonna do?
How could this be the one spot
that there's absolutely
no service?
Zoey, Zoey, hey, hey.
I think we can make it,
but we have to go.
We have to walk now.
-Okay.
-Come on.
Yeah, it'll be good.
Here we go.
Have you heard from Chase
this morning?
Nobody can get
a hold of him.
No, I haven't.
Wow, you look so good.
Thanks. So do you.
-Have you heard from Zoey?
-No, I haven't.
Wait. Is this supposed
to be their first look?
- They're weird like that.
- Wait.
So the maid of honor and
the best man are both missing?
I can't believe this.
How much farther?
Oh. Here.
Okay. Thank you.
Here, you wear mine.
Oh, that's so much better.
Yeah, this is...
-This is not better.
-Okay.
Oh, God.
So normally I could not
afford Montecito,
but I can afford Montecito
if the house has had a murder,
-which this one has.
-Uh-huh.
-The whole first floor--
-I think that might be wet.
What is that?
Uh, it's "White Diamond,"
Mr. Kevyn.
Benjamin Moore?
This is a great shade.
I mean, I love it.
Will you paint my office
that color?
-Yeah.
-Great. Now?
-Oh. Yeah. Yes, sir.
-Now!
No, in the future. Now!
-Greg!
-Hi, hi.
Hey.
Does anyone have eyes
on the car?
Oh, God.
Come on, we gotta go.
We gotta go.
Okay.
-Hello?
-Oh, my God!
I thought you were dead!
I hoped you were dead!
I've called you
like a thousand times.
-Where the hell are you?
-I know, I know.
So I didn't exactly realize that
the car needed to be charged.
So it's dead on the side
of the PCH.
Oh, my God!
But it's okay.
The car doesn't even
need to be there...
because Jordan B. is going
to listen to what I say.
How are you gonna tell him what
to say if you're not here?
Archer, you're gonna
have to trust me on this one.
Well, I actually don't.
Um...
I didn't mean to eavesdrop,
but it sounds like
you've gotten yourself into
quite a complicated situation.
You have no idea.
Okay, we have waited
as long as we can, all right?
These guests are gonna leave
if we have to listen to Lyric
sing anymore.
Wait.
We're here.
And we have the rings.
Quinn, I'm so sorry.
I can explain.
No. No explanations, all right?
We are late enough as it is.
Places. Go. Go.
Cue Lyric.
Cue me.
And cue Michael and Mark.
* This *
* Is my gift to you *
* A song *
* For your day brand-new *
Cue Camille and Jared.
* Written *
* By me *
* For you *
* You together *
* She's in her wedding dress *
* And he's hoping
she'll say yes... *
I was really worried
about you.
I know. I'm so sorry.
* I wrote it for the both... *
And Zoey and Chase.
* Ooh *
* I just want you both
to know *
* That I wrote this song *
* Yeah, I wrote this song *
Thirty seconds to showtime.
Thirty seconds, everybody.
Hey, what am I supposed to do?
Are you seriously
asking me that?
-Yes.
-If you pick a Pontiac over me
on live television,
I will make your life
a living hell, hmm?
Hey, pal.
Pre-show jitters
are totally normal, okay?
Here's what I want you to do.
Just relax and listen to Zoey.
-Can you do that for me?
-I think so.
You're gonna be great.
-Oh, who's Zoey?
-She's not here, dude.
You'll have to manage this
on your own.
-Nice hair, by the way.
-Thanks.
-Fifteen seconds.
-Wow, okay, Joey. Thank you.
And paging Zoey.
Zoey, do you copy?
Where's the girl?
I'm here. I'm here, Jordan.
You got this, buddy.
Just take a deep breath for me.
This should be fun.
Please rise.
Welcome to
the LOVE: Fully Charged
season six live finale!
I'm your host, Archer March.
Three couples remain.
But only one can win.
And that couple will soon
be revealed.
First, let's look
at some highlights
from this juicy season.
Love you.
You may be seated.
No?
Dearly beloved...
Are you ready, America?
I don't know about you,
but my heart is racing.
Ugh, I'm sorry.
I just hate their faces.
Is it just me?
Don't-- I'd like you
not to answer.
...of two of my very favorite
people in the world.
A genius, whose discoveries
will define a generation,
and my rich friend,
Logan Reese.
the winners of LOVE:
Fully Charged season six are...
Jordan B. and Jordyn J.!
Congratulations, you guys.
Wow. This is so well-deserved.
How are you feeling right now?
Uh...
Say, "It wouldn't
have been possible
without this beautiful woman."
It wouldn't have been possible
without this beautiful woman.
Aw!
Oh, um, did the maid of honor
have something
she wanted to say?
Oh, no! God!
Sorry.
I'm just so overwhelmed
with emotion.
Uh-huh. Um, as I was saying...
Sorry, I'm just so overwhelmed
with emotion.
Okay, well, um,
don't get too excited,
because it's not over yet.
You still have a very big
decision to make.
Tight on the garage.
Perfect. Very nice.
Should anyone present
know of any reason
that this couple should not
be joined in holy matrimony,
speak now or forever
hold your peace.
Stacey.
You.
It's you.
Mark.
Hugo.
You were right under my nose.
How did I not see it sooner?
First, you came to the welcome
reception in dirty scrubs,
and no self-respecting ER doctor
would ever leave the hospital
in dirty scrubs.
Two, you said you were
from Burbank,
which is not in Australia.
And also...
you have massive hands.
Hey, look...
Everyone, this man
is not the charming,
selfless, hilarious,
extremely jacked Hemsworth
cousin that we all thought.
This man is the Malibu Murderer!
Wait, wait? Murderer?
No, no, no, no. I...
I'm not a murderer.
I'm an actor.
Jordan B., what do you love most
about Jordyn J.?
-What's going on?
-Nothing, absolutely nothing.
Nothing, absolutely nothing.
Jordan B.,
we're all a little confused.
What is it that you really want?
If it's absolutely nothing,
then why were you late?
It was the car! The car!
No, Jordan, not you.
The car. Oh, the car!
Can you explain all of this?
Yes. Sorry. Of course.
Am I hearing you correctly?
You're choosing the car?
Yes. Sorry. Of course.
Open the garage, I guess.
Where is the car?
Where is the effing car?
Greg?
Are you watching
LOVE: Fully Charged ?
Oh! Who won?
What is going on?
I'm working.
I'm working during your wedding.
I got an opportunity,
and I tried to do both.
If you had to work,
why didn't you just tell me?
Because this is so important,
and you were so excited.
So I lied. To myself, to you.
To everyone.
What about him?
What is Stacey talking about?
Hugo is not a murderer.
I'm not sure how she came
to that conclusion.
His name is Todd,
and I hired him to be
my boyfriend for the weekend.
I knew something
was going on with you.
You've been distant
and distracted,
and you completely abandoned me
when I needed you the most.
To do what? Hang out with Chase?
Zoey, you should be
ashamed of yourself.
Logan, don't even start.
You care more about
making this wedding a spectacle
than about making it meaningful.
You completely ignored me
every step of the way.
None of this is what I wanted.
Our wedding is off.
* If I'm so smart *
* Why do I feel so dumb? *
* Why did you take *
* My heart *
* Then just cut and run? *
* And if the pain is real *
* Why do I feel so numb? *
* And if I'm so smart... *
I don't know what's happening.
I don't know
what's happening.
I could do
everyone's job in here
better than everyone who
is not doing their job in here.
Everyone's fired. Get out.
* ...feel so down *
* Why do I see *
So I guess this is a wrap
on me then, huh?
Yeah. Thanks for everything
this weekend.
I'm so sorry I dragged you
into all this,
and I can't even
get you on the show.
I'm an actor in L.A.
I kind of expect
to be disappointed.
You got my head shot
and resume?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
* If I'm so high *
* Why do I feel so down? *
* And if I'm so brave *
* Why do I feel so scared? *
* Why did you tell me stay *
* Then just disappear *
* And if it's true *
* You're going *
* Why do I still
feel you here? *
* So long, farewell *
* Goodbye *
-Hey.
So, did you talk to Danielle?
I mean, I feel awful.
Zoey, I...
I have a confession.
Danielle and I actually broke up
two weeks ago.
She agreed to still
come with me to the wedding
so I didn't have
to show up alone.
Well, at least you didn't
hire an actor.
Yeah, there's that.
How did I screw this up so bad,
and when did life get so messy?
I know we thought
high school was hard,
but I would kill
to go back to PCA.
Yeah, it's too bad Quinn hasn't
invented a time machine yet.
I'm sure we'd all love
to go back.
Yeah.
Go back.
That's exactly
what we need to do.
Uh, what?
This is gonna take a while.
All right, people,
let's get to work.
Let's do it.
Think there's anything left
in the old
arts and crafts studio?
You know, this is great and all,
but what if I can't
get her here?
I've tried flower arrangements,
edible arrangements,
a sky writer, nothing.
Have you tried talking to her?
-No!
-Maybe try that.
-There's so much to do.
-I know. I know.
Do you mind helping Ms. Reese
with lights over there?
Thank you.
I don't know, Mark!
Just be helpful!
-I'm trying.
-Here, I'll help.
-Thank you.
-Got it.
Zoey!
Look what I found!
No, no, you're under strict
vocal rest until it's time.
Is this cake?
-Yeah.
-I knew it.
Okay, okay.
Okay, listen,
I know that we thought
Sushi Rox closed
when the school did,
but it turns out Kazu's son
started a food truck,
and they'd be more than happy
to cater.
Perfect. She loves sushi.
Cool, I think
that covers everything, right?
Except for music.
I know that Quinn was really
excited about the band,
but unfortunately
they're unavailable today.
So who are we gonna get
to play the music?
Me.
I'm a DJ too.
* You're welcome *
Sounds pretty good.
That settles it.
So, what do we do now?
Now? We wait.
I'm so sorry, Quinn!
Maybe this all happened
for a reason.
Maybe we just want
different things.
-And maybe that's okay.
-No!
I don't want different things.
I only want what you want.
I was trying so hard
to make this wedding perfect
for me and for you.
I stopped thinking about us.
I was an idiot.
I was worse than an idiot.
I was--
A groomzilla?
Yes.
Is that a thing?
All I know is I want
to be with you...
because I love you, Quinn.
I love you too, Logan.
I love Quinn Pensky!
And I love Logan Reese!
Shut up!
Hang on, I'll buzz you up.
Can you come down?
I was hoping we could go
for a ride.
Logan, where are we?
What are we doing?
Hi.
What is all this?
Did you do this?
We all did.
Quinn, I'm so sorry.
You can't not marry
your best friend
because your other best friend
ruined it.
But I'm wearing this.
Well, you did always say
that you'd rather get married
in a lab coat.
Here.
How do you feel?
Like myself.
Quinn Pensky...
will you marry me still?
-Yes?
-Yeah.
Yes! Yes!
She said yes.
Dearly beloved.
Just kidding!
We're gathered here today
to celebrate this beautiful love
between Quinn Pensky
and Logan Reese.
Seriously, best ceremony
I've ever heard.
I mean, hilarious,
heartbreaking, personal.
Did you write that yourself?
I've been writing that
since high school
when they first fell in love.
You should do our wedding.
Oh, I'm down.
Let's do it. Let's go!
Oh, excuse me.
I have to take this.
Kelley, I know
what you're going to say,
and my stuff will be out
of the office on Monday.
I'm promoting you.
You're what?
The numbers are in.
It was the highest-rated
Fully Charged
finale ever.
The network is sharting
their brains with happiness.
They want a spin-off
with both Jordans.
I want you on my team.
-I don't know what to say.
-There is so much more to you
than meets the eye.
You have so much more
to offer.
What you did by throwing out
every reality TV trope,
by ignoring me at every turn,
that took balls.
I respect balls.
-You're right.
-What?
I do have a lot to offer.
And I'm tired of wasting it
on people who don't deserve it,
like you.
-I quit.
-I'll double your salary.
-And give me the corner office?
-Yeah, sure.
And fire Greg?
-Hey, Greg?
-What?
You're fired.
All right.
- Yeah, done.
- Oh, there he is! Todd!
One more thing.
Deal.
Hey, Jordan?
Go home.
I don't know where I live!
I am sorry that I accused you
of being a murderer,
but you have to understand
it was not my fault.
It was Mark's.
Mark, what did you do?
I followed a bad lead.
That's right. And what do you
have to say to Quinn?
I am sorry
we ruined your wedding?
We?
I'm sorry I ruined your wedding.
Better.
Oh, I am also very sorry,
but he does not speak for me.
No, it's a feminism thing.
We do that--
Where are you going?
Todd, you made it.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
I manny on the weekends.
Well, you may not
have to anymore,
because I got you on the show!
-No.
-Yes!
Thank you!
Everybody, get out of the way.
Quinn and my dumb brother
are gonna do their first dance.
-So...
-Tell me.
This wedding sucks.
Where are the oyster shuckers?
All right, I deserved that.
* I *
* Don't know *
* Don't care *
-* Won't go *
-Phew.
You want to dance?
* You say *
What's next, Chase Matthews?
Back to Baltimore?
You know,
it is really cold out there.
Well, I heard,
and don't quote me,
but I heard there are schools
in California.
Oh, well...
Well, maybe I'll look into that.
But whatever the future holds...
I hope that you're in it.
Because...
I love you, Zoey.
And I always have.
I...
love you too.
Ugh, I'm bored.
* Starships were meant to fly *
* Hands up and touch the sky *
* Can't stop,
'cause we're so high *
* Let's do this one more time *
* Starships were meant to fly *
* Hands up and touch the sky *
* Let's do this one last time *
* Can't stop,
we're higher than a mother... *
Toss it back! Woo!
* We're higher
than a mother... *
* Starships were meant
to fly... *
I hear you're, like,
a producer.
Heard of Drippin' ?
And you're friends with Logan?
And he didn't
introduce me to you?
Logan, you always do this to me!
You never support me
in any of my endeavors!
I support you. Don't--
* Starships were meant to fly *
Good for you for picking up
on the rebound, you know?
Yeah!
-Yeah. Yeah!
-Yeah.
Sloppy seconds.
* Can't stop,
we're higher than a mother... *
* We're higher
than a mother... *
I know you're bummed we didn't
catch him this time, Stace,
but we will.
We always do.
That's why we're the number one
murder podcast in America.
Yeah.
You're probably right.
So great meeting you, Todd.
Sorry again
about that little mix-up.
Oh, don't even worry about it.
You guys get home safe, okay?
Shh.
I have ideas.
Excuse me, did I wink?
You're loving it, Mr. Perry.
Oh, I am.
Mr. Perry,
you own a jewelry shop.
I'm loving it too.
Bubbe! What are you doing?
Oh, I thought you were cake.
-No, it's me.
-I almost ate you.
Here, I got your back.
Oh, my God!
-We're in a car!
-It didn't smell bad.
Somebody help me. My God.
With a 300-mile driving radius--
Uh-huh, what's the line?
I'm sorry to this camera
that has to go back and forth.
Loving you.
* Yeah, yeah *
* Tell the DJ... *
And...
Could you play that back?
* Yeah *
Are you guys still filming me?
Can I ask an honest question?
Can you tell that these are
ladies' leggings?
I don't think you can tell.
Right?
* Yeah, yeah *
I'm good.
Cut.
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not.
And that's that.
* Inside your head *
* Just get out
with me instead *
* Let's melt the stress away *
* Yeah, yeah *
* Yeah, yeah, you *
* Do what you want to do *
* Be your own kind of muse *
* It's your role to play *
* Yeah, yeah *
* Tell the DJ play *
* We can dance all day *
* Let's just get away, yeah *
* We can make them see *
* All of the things
that we can be *
* Forget all your fears
and follow me *
* Yeah, yeah, yeah *
* The stars are shining now *
* They're shining for you *
* Shining for you *
* But you don't need
shooting stars *
* The magic's all in you *
* We can make them see *
* All of the things
that we can be *
* Forget all your fears
and follow me *
* Yeah, yeah, yeah *
* Tell the DJ play *
* We can dance all day *
* Let's just get away *
* Yeah *
* We can make them see *
* All of the things
that we can be *
* Forget all your fears
and follow me *